<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Dress Code</title><description>Style, Demystified</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Dress Code</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 3.1</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 16:31:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Fun Poses in Menswear</title><description>These guys dance, play, eat, drink, finger-gun... They make their photos stand out, they highlight what's great about their clothes, and they have fun doing it.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/fun-poses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ebd3ab94a4a84089d43f35a</guid><category>fun</category><category>inspo</category><category>dancing</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 16:31:12 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Interview-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Interview-1.jpg" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/KoRaehm"&gt;tl;dr imgur album&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm a fan of candid photography. Posing for photos can look and feel awkward. Unfortunately, in Menswear, it's a necessary evil. Evil, that is, unless you &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; know how to pose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't. But you know who does? Jamie, Ethan and Marco. These guys dance, play, eat, drink, finger-gun... They make their photos stand out, they highlight what's great about their clothes, and they have fun doing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-thrust.jpg" width="1080" height="1350" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Ballet.jpg" width="1080" height="1350" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Dancing.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Jamie goes through a range of movements highlighting the drape of his blazers, the flex in his shoes, and the folly of athleisure—you can move in anything, people!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="jamieferguson"&gt;Jamie Ferguson&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A photographer by trade, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/jkf_man/"&gt;Jamie Ferguson&lt;/a&gt; found himself with a lot of free time in quarantine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His solution to this lack of client work was to experiment with new lighting techniques, whatever props he had handy, and, as you can tell, some very animated poses. He and his moustache made goofy faces, danced like nobody was shooting, and... ate, and drank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Drinking-1.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Sad-1.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Drinking-Glass-1.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Eating-1.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Eating is weird.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating and drinking are weird. Eating in particular is a strange activity -- it's one we're conditioned to associate with vulnerability. The adrenal response is our &amp;quot;fight and flight&amp;quot; response -- it represents us at our strongest and fastest. But digestion and rest are quite opposed; we do these things when we know we're safe. This deeply ingrained association has created many shy eaters -- people cover their mouths when they eat. Characters in movies and on TV sit at a dinner table but generally aren't actually seen eating. Eating is intimate; it's something we do on dates. So think about it: how often do you see photos of people eating?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So when you &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; to look a little vulnerable -- or to look downright goofy -- eating is a really unique, unusual, and powerful way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't for the faint of heart. Most of us don't have Jamie's talent as a photographer or model. This series of photos reflects the creativity and skill required for both photography and modeling. But if you're feeling like a new challenge for your fit pics -- grab some goofy-looking food, and try to look good eating it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of eating, let's talk about...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Ethan-Eating-2.jpg" width="640" height="960" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Etahn-Eating-1.jpg" width="640" height="960" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Ethan-Boba-Snort.jpg" width="1024" height="1544" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;"I'm just naturally dumb." – Ethan M. Wong, 2020&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="ethanmwong"&gt;Ethan M. Wong&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ethanmwong/"&gt;Ethan&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://streetxsprezza.wordpress.com/"&gt;Street x Sprezza&lt;/a&gt; knows how to eat on camera. Again, Ethan is a photographer. He's framed these photos carefully, and he's framed them well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there's a good deal more candor in Ethan's photos. He doesn't really even think of it as posing. He feels silly, he hands his friends a camera, and he just... acts the way he acts. You need a bit of personality to do this, and you need some friends who are willing to take a dumb photo and not question it. That's trickier than it sounds -- when I tell my friends to take candid photos of me, they get confused and ask me to pose. By the time they figure out what I want, the moment's gone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, you're probably not surrounded with friends right now, but you can at least attempt to recreate this magic with a tripod and a timer. But if you ask me, as long as you control the camera, you're posing, and that's exactly what you're trying to get away from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethan's gang has got the magic formula figured out. He knows how to be his own precious self, and they know how to capture it without ruining it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Ethan-Telephone.jpg" width="640" height="960" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Ethan-Cameras-1.jpg" width="640" height="959" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/SAD-Bois-Dancing-2.jpg" width="2048" height="1365" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Etahn-Animated.jpg" width="640" height="960" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Ethan's crew... They run a &lt;a href="https://soundcloud.com/styleanddirection"&gt;podcast&lt;/a&gt; (and &lt;a href="https://www.twitch.tv/styleanddirection"&gt;Twitch channel&lt;/a&gt;) called &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/styleanddirection/"&gt;Style and Direction&lt;/a&gt;. Check 'em out, and stay tuned for their Patreon launch in June.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime... Prepare for new levels of strange.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Marco-2.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Marco-1.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Marco-4.jpg" width="1080" height="1080" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Marco-3.jpg" width="1080" height="1080" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Marco can &lt;em&gt;dance&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="marcomartinez"&gt;Marco Martinez&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p0cketman/"&gt;Marco&lt;/a&gt;, aka &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/kamotejoe"&gt;/u/kamotejoe&lt;/a&gt;, can dance. And somehow, he can dance well enough that even the still photos of him dancing look cool. Again, we are faced with the unfortunate fact that these great poses require hard work, natural talent, and style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His style is... Quite obviously, weird. Engineered Garments, Needles, Kapital, and a bunch of other strange brands coalesce into one of the most unique wardrobes out there. But he just has so much fun with it, and that's infectious. It took me a while, but it's really not that hard to see why he's one of Reddit's favorites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reddit loves Marco so much that, when he suggested a &amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/glhy54/mfa_theme_waywt_challenge_freaky_friday/"&gt;Freaky Friday&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; theme thread, many users decided to dress, and pose, as him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Fluxknot-as-Marco.jpg" width="1920" height="3414" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Bond-as-Marco.jpg" width="3001" height="2000" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Manliftingbanner-as-Marco.jpg" width="2220" height="3108" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;/u/fluxknot, Eric M. Cotecson (/u/bond__jamesbond), and /u/manliftingbanner, all playing as Marco for MFA's "Freaky Friday" thread.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you thought they imitated Marco because it would be easy, I've got bad news for you -- he's been dancing for 9 years, and he still goes to classes. And not only that, but he's constantly thinking about his clothing when he poses. He's thinking about what lines his movements will highlight. While &lt;em&gt;also&lt;/em&gt; having fun and doing what comes natural to him. Does that sound like a paradox?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His advice is encouraging, but not in the way you want it to be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like all things it takes time but even small improvements should be celebrated. The most important place to start is to learn to relax and lean into the groove + music when dancing. Every dance style has a specific groove that brings it to life which is why most dance classes start with a groove warmup. Because we're given so many messages by society to &amp;quot;fit in,&amp;quot; dancing is a fundamental reprogramming of things we've picked up and is actually an act of rebellion. Hence, why most famous dance styles like breaking, locking, vogue, and house started within marginalized urban communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I wouldn't sweat trying to dance like a pro dancer because effort and feeling matter so much more than &amp;quot;looking good&amp;quot; and I think that concept is not fair to attach to something as subjective as dance. It's important to feel great above all, energy permeates through to other people more than how &amp;quot;good&amp;quot; one looks. That's my long-winded way of saying that finding what works at a pace comfortable to you is the most important!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Awesome. I'll keep trying this for nine years and if I take a good photo between now and then, I'll just consider it a bonus. I'll share my failures in the meantime -- I'll attach a couple below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more on Marco, see &lt;a href="https://www.grailed.com/drycleanonly/community-collections-marco-martinez"&gt;his profile on Grailed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/JFK-Finger-Guns.jpg" width="1440" height="1800" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Spencer-Finger-Guns-1.jpg" width="640" height="960" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Woah, put those things away fellas.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="takeaways"&gt;Takeaways&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I set out writing this article hoping I'd be able to give you some good advice on how to pose in more unique ways, or learn how to do it better myself. You can see how well that turned out below -- I'm sharing my failures just for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the biggest lesson is that... Art is hard work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honesty is a part of it. You have to get comfortable in front of a camera, you have to be a naturally silly person. And you need some raw talent. But then you need to work at it. Remember that film is cheap, and that you're probably not using any. That, if today's photos are a little better than yesterday's, then you're making progress. And that maybe, one day, you can look as fly on camera as these crazy fucks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So try your best. Get your funky flow going. Take those photos like nobody's watching, and then post them, even when they're bad. Send me your attempts, if you have some you're proud of, and we'll see -- maybe I'll find a chance do an article like this again, with a few new friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/KoRaehm"&gt;here's the imgur album&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now get ready to laugh at me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Me-Capoeira.jpg" width="1080" height="1439" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Me-Meditating.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/05/Me-Dancing.jpeg" width="1469" height="1958" alt="Fun Poses in Menswear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Do as I say, not as I do.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>How Formal is Formalwear?</title><description>While it's mired in tradition and rules, I'm going to take this opportunity to express something about eveningwear: I'm going to explain the odd sense in which eveningwear is *more casual* than lounge suiting.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/how-formal-is-formalwear/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e9c5749aac91109aaebd9e8</guid><category>eveningwear</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>loud</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 22:29:31 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Mathias-Lefevre-Morocco.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Mathias-Lefevre-Morocco.jpg" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you're new to menswear or steeped in it, you've no doubt seen some sliding scale of formality with extreme casual all the way on the left, and either the tuxedo or white tie all the way on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a simplified view at something that's far more complex than the one dimension with which you've been presented. As you want to progress, you'll want to consider not only the factors that make a thing more formal or casual, but the various senses in which a thing might be more formal or casual, and which further your intent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it's mired in tradition and rules -- the black tie dress code is extremely specific -- I'm going to take this opportunity to express something about eveningwear: I'm going to explain the odd sense in which eveningwear is &lt;em&gt;more casual&lt;/em&gt; than lounge suiting. And I think we can all learn something from that perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Particularly, I'm going to focus on the fact that eveningwear is flashy, the sense in which it signals a partying mood, and sense in which it relates to and echoes loungewear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Daniel-Craig.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Daniel Craig as James Bond.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="eveningwearisflashy"&gt;Eveningwear is flashy.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lounge suit is generally composed of matte wool or some other material with no more than a minimal sheen. It generally has notch lapels and horn buttons. You wear it with a buttoned shirt, calfskin leathers, and often a belt. It's generally built to help you look good, but blend in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But on a tuxedo, the lapels are covered in satin or grosgrain. It has peak or shawl lapels for the grabbing of attention. The buttons are covered in felt or silk or something similarly smooth. You wear a shirt with a covered placket, a bow tie, and a waist covering to ensure that there is no white interruption below the button point, as opposed to a belt that would constitute such an interruption. Your footwear is either the eye-grabbing patent leather or velvet -- you're trying to exude luxury. Everything about eveningwear demands attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is especially evident in events with creative black tie dress codes; while peoples' lounge suits are rarely loud, the second you lift the strict limits of black tie, people get &lt;em&gt;weird&lt;/em&gt; with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Luka-Sabbat-Met-Gala-2018.jpg" width="1080" height="1620" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Ansel-Elgort-Met-Gala-2018.jpg" width="1080" height="1651" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Chadwick-Boseman-Met-Gala-2018.jpg" width="1080" height="1720" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Donald-Glover-Met-Gala-2018.jpg" width="1080" height="1625" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Luka Sabbat, Ansel Elgort, Chadwick Boseman and Donald Glover, all at the Met Gala 2018. Sorry, creative black tie events are few and far between these days, and this was one of the better-photographed events. Well, Luka's photo appears to have been taken before the event, but that's what he wore.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when you want to expand your casual wardrobe, consider, using flashier elements -- silk, or its more manageable cousin rayon. Velvet and other pile fabrics. Anything with an unusual sheen. Think about whether, and in what ways, you want to stand out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="youwearabusinesssuitforbusinessyouweareveningweartoparty"&gt;You wear a business suit for business. You wear eveningwear to party.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you go to a wedding in the same suit you wear for an interview, you're going to look the way you look in an interview. You're going to look like you're there to do business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Tuxedo stands out, not just because it's flashy, but because it's unusual. Nobody wears a tuxedo to the office. Nobody wears a tuxedo to a grocery store. If you see somebody in a tuxedo, you know he's there to party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Somehow, even when the jacket comes off, and you're in a bow tie and suspenders, you don't look like Steve Urkel -- you still look like you were born on the dance floor. At some point in the night, you'll undo the bowtie, grab a whiskey or a cigar, and feel like you're in The Godfather. The whole rig just represents this classic, romantic, perfect ideal of man at his best and happiest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Sebastian-McFox.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B73A815BLy4"&gt;Sebastian McFox&lt;/a&gt; via Instagram&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Donald-Glover-Gucci-Emmys-2017.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Donald Glover at the 2017 Emmy Awards&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;So don't just think about your occasion in terms of how formal it is, but what the spirit is. Is it a serious occasion, or a fun one? Are you here to work -- whether in business casual or workwear and denim -- or to chill, or to party? Each of these mindsets can be explored through suiting or more casual attire, and is important to consider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="tuxedosarelinkedtoclassicloungewear"&gt;Tuxedos are linked to classic loungewear.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compare the Dinner Jacket to the Smoking Jacket; compare the Smoking Jacket to the Dressing Gown. Compare Prince Albert slippers to Smoking slippers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's this whole subclass of high-end luxury loungewear -- clothing that's practically similar to black tie, but meant to be worn by either wealthy or unreasonably proper men, exclusively in their homes. It's the kind of thing you'd wear if you threw a house party and wanted to feel just a little bit like Hugh Heffner -- just a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A nice soft shawl lapel helps echo this vibe more, where a peak lapel will better reflect the formal spirit you're probably still grappling with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/04/Mathias-Lefevre.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="How Formal is Formalwear?"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6s7hDJg616/"&gt;Mathias le Fèvre&lt;/a&gt; via Instagram. Also consider the Luka Sabbat look from above.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;How might you dress this down from a full tuxedo, but up from actual loungewear? A belt or tie can also be very helpful. A shawl collar cardigan can be soft; a silky noragi might flow in the way you want it to. Velvet, again, can work nicely. Your shoes should be slip ons, maybe suede.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the world gets more casual, we see fewer and fewer black tie dress codes. People have small daytime weddings in lounge suits. And by all means -- do what you want, especially at your wedding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I think we're missing something. I think we're giving up a dress code that isn't old and stuffy -- like I believe White Tie and Morning Dress to be -- but sleek and fun in all the best ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, it's expensive, and we don't want to expect our guests to spend a few hundred dollars on a creative black tie rig here and there. Black Tie Optional is a good middle ground, but it's a bit of a schizophrenic dress code since eveningwear and lounge suits feel so different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I don't think we're about to see an eveningwear revival. But if we could reimagine it as something more accessible, the spirit of eveningwear is an important one I think we need to keep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So consider the principles of casualness embodied here. Consider buying more flashy menswear, silk and velvet -- or perhaps more wearable cousins like rayon and corduroy. Consider pieces that announce your intention to party. Wear suede slippers, or kilim slippers, or belgian loafers. Wear clothing that exhibits comfort -- a silky noragi or a thick, soft, belted, shawl collar cardigan. Wear anything you wouldn't normally wear, and take eveningwear as a bit of inspiration towards that ideal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear</title><description>TL;DR: buy the UnderTwills, particularly the boxers. The shirts are fine at bundle prices,but nothing to write home about.
</description><link>http://localhost:2368/initial-impressions-twillory-stuff/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e4fd9c367fc44125575727c</guid><category>impressions</category><category>dress shirts</category><category>undershirts</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>underwear</category><category>menswear</category><category>neckwear</category><category>performance</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 20:05:07 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer-1.jpg" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: buy the UnderTwills, particularly the boxers. The shirts are fine at bundle prices, but nothing to write home about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey all. No clever intro this time -- &lt;a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ"&gt;Twillory&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;) just sent me a solid bunch of stuff to review. The shirts and underwear here were all given to me at no cost in consideration of my review. At the bottom, I'll throw in a few shots of my old wool tie from Twillory, which I (kind of) paid for -- more on that further down.Hey all. No clever intro this time -- &lt;a href="http://"&gt;Twillory&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;) just sent me a solid bunch of stuff to review. The shirts and underwear here were all given to me at no cost in consideration of my review. At the bottom, I'll throw in a few shots of my old wool tie from Twillory, which I (kind of) paid for -- more on that further down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I have some coupons: &lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/SUNHR01GR0lDSEZIT0hOQ0dJRkdJSg"&gt;buy one and get one free shirts&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.pntra.com/t/SUNISEdHR01DSEZIT0hOQ0dJRkdJSg"&gt;$20 off your first purchase of shirts/pants&lt;/a&gt;. Unfortunately, these don't cover the good shit -- the undertwills -- but they're decent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that They didn't ask for any special treatment here, and I ain't givin' it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Purple-Hayes-Fit.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Purple-Hayes-Close.jpg" width="1080" height="1080" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Purple-Hayes.jpg" width="1080" height="1439" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="1purplehayesshirtinnonironsafecotton100cotton"&gt;1. &amp;quot;Purple Hayes&amp;quot; Shirt in Non-Iron &amp;quot;SafeCotton&amp;quot; (100% Cotton)&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Item&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/Qz9JR0pEP0RCREtESj9JR0pE?url=https%3A%2F%2Ftwillory.com%2Fproducts%2Fnon-iron-purple-hayes"&gt;SafeCotton Dress Shirt in &amp;quot;Purple Hayes&amp;quot; Check&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/collections/safecotton/products/non-iron-purple-hayes"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: 100% Cotton Twill&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: 15.5/32-33 Tailored Fit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These shirts normally go for $99 each, but get much cheaper when you buy 2-4, down as low as $57 each for 4+. I also have a coupon that lets you &lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/SUNHR01GR0lDSEZIT0hOQ0dJRkdJSg"&gt;buy one and get one free&lt;/a&gt;, and also there's some kind of free gift involved I don't know anything about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This fabric is... Different. It's very soft, but sort of... coarse. It's overall nicer than the stiff poplins and twills I have from Charles Tyrwhitt and Bonobos, but I often notice it brush against my skin, and when I do, I'm just not sure how I feel. It reminds me of my wool-blend shirt from Hilditch &amp;amp; Key, except that one is pretty disappointing -- I only wear it with an undershirt -- whereas this fabric is... good, just strange. I'm curious to see how it feels after a few washes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They use a different treatment from the typical formaldehyde-based treatment used to make non-iron shirts. They brag about the chemicals they don't use, but there shouldn't be anything particularly dangerous about typical non-iron treatments -- the amount of formaldehyde that might reach even the surface of your skin is pretty negligible -- so they just happen to be doing something a little different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other details are pretty nice. The collar is a respectable spread. The stitching seems good. The collar stays, while not especially important, are a really nice, thick, brushed nickel, with a pattern engraved on one side. The buttons are a thick plastic resin, which... At these prices, you could start looking for mother of pearl buttons, most notably from Brooks Brothers (who I'd describe as their closest price competitor -- you might have to buy clearance or wait for a sale, but it shouldn't be hard to get 4/$200 shirts from Brooks Brothers). But Mother of Pearl isn't a big deal -- it's more just a classic menswear standard than anything. With the &lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/SUNHR01GR0lDSEZIT0hOQ0dJRkdJSg"&gt;bogo+gift coupon&lt;/a&gt;, that's a pretty good deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's worth noting that they offer a lot of interesting patterns, but not a lot of simple ones. I actually couldn't find a solid pale pink shirt on their site, which I think of as a bit of a standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notes on Sizing: overall fits similar to the equivalent Charles Tyrwhitt, but a little slimmer, as the size charts indicate. But the sleeves are long. I normally go for 32, so I thought 32-33 should be fine, but they're definitely long, probably by more than an inch, on both shirts. Oh well -- for now, I'm wearing sweaters over them anyway, and in spring/summer, I'll probably just roll my sleeves up. I might tailor them, but as for buying more -- sleeve sizing would be a big enough issue to stop me. But sizing is possible, and if you can find a size you like, go for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer-Sweater.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer-Fit.jpg" width="1080" height="1442" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mixer-Sleeve.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Yeah, without the sweater, these sleeves are disastrously long. I'll roll them up in the summer and survive.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="2mixerperformancedressshirt"&gt;2. &amp;quot;Mixer&amp;quot; Performance Dress Shirt&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Item&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twillory.com%2Fcollections%2Fperformance%2Fproducts%2Fperformance-mixer"&gt;Performance Dress shirt in &amp;quot;Mixer&amp;quot; Windowpane&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/collections/performance/products/performance-mixer"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: Roughly 64% Cotton, 21% Spandex, 11% Coolmax (a particular type of Nylon), 4% spandex. Twill weave.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: 15.5/32-33 Tailored Fit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These shirts normally go for $99 each, but get much cheaper when you buy 2-4, down as low as $57 each for 4+. I also have a coupon that lets you &lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/SUNHR01GR0lDSEZIT0hOQ0dJRkdJSg"&gt;buy one and get one free&lt;/a&gt;, and also there's some kind of free gift involved I don't know anything about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: I don't have a lot of experience with performance dress shirts. I'm the type of guy who tends to prefer natural materials, but figured that would be a useful perspective. For more detail, the Kavalier has a review, and also mentions Twillory in &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r2rb_dixLAQ"&gt;his latest performance dress shirt roundup&lt;/a&gt;. He's a fan, but to be fair, he's a fan of most of the things he's ever been near.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So as for my perspective... I don't love it. The fabric is stretchy, but it's not soft in the way I expect pure cotton to be. I don't have a particular need for stretch. Maybe it'll prove its value after I throw it in the wash, or in the summer when I can put the breathability to the test.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It uses the same nice buttons and collar stays as the cotton shirt, and fits the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also added some kind padding to the inside cuffs and part of the back... That actually feels quite nice on my skin, although I don't particularly want the gray contrast showing when I roll my sleeves up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/UnderTwills.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Undershirt (left) and Boxers (right). Don't worry, I won't be modeling these..&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="3performanceundershirt"&gt;3. Performance Undershirt&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Item&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.pntra.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twillory.com%2Fcollections%2Fundertwills%2Fproducts%2Fundertwills-performance-vneck"&gt;Performance Undershirt // V Neck&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/collections/undertwills/products/undertwills-performance-vneck"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;) in white.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: 47% Cotton / 47% Rayon / 6% Spandex&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: Medium&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$24 for one, $36 for 2, or &lt;a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twillory.com%2Fcollections%2Fundertwills%2Fproducts%2Fperformance-undertwills-4-pack"&gt;$14.50/shirt at 4+&lt;/a&gt;. Can be combo'd with boxer briefs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, so this one, I get. Undershirts, since they're supposed to fit closer to the body, actually need some stretch. And they used rayon! Now rayon feels good on the skin. This undershirt is cool, breathable, and pleasant. It's cut long, so it can stay tucked in, and is just deep enough a v to stay hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two downsides: one, it only comes in white. Gray is generally the least visible color for an undershirt, so that's what I'd prefer. But I haven't actually had an issue with this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the price. At $24 per, they're not quite impulse buys. But at the multi-buy price -- $14.50 for 4+ -- I really complain, especially for such a nice fabric blend. I'd say they are a better value than uniqlo airism at that price, but I haven't actually tested them in the heat yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="4performanceboxerbriefs"&gt;4. Performance Boxer Briefs&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Item&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.pntrac.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twillory.com%2Fcollections%2Fundertwills%2Fproducts%2Fundertwills-performance-boxer-briefs-gray"&gt;Performance Boxer Briefs // Grey&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.twillory.com/collections/undertwills/products/undertwills-performance-boxer-briefs-gray"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: 90% modal (which is a type of rayon), 10% spandex&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: Medium&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$24 for one, $36 for 2, or &lt;a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/TUJGRUlLRUJHRUdOR01CRkhFRkhJ?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.twillory.com%2Fcollections%2Fundertwills%2Fproducts%2Fperformance-undertwills-4-pack"&gt;$14.50/pair at 4+&lt;/a&gt;. Can be combo'd with undershirts. These are also available in black.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay so here's the good shit. My first day in these was fine -- the fabric was nice, but they rode up a bit. But after that, they learned to stay put, and... Oh man, they might as well be silk. Soft and luxurious, but with more stretch and breathability than silk would offer. I mean, I like modal, and I haven't compared this to many of the top competitors in the $24 range, but... Even early on, I can tell, I'm probably going to buy 4 more of these at some point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These don't have any weird gimmicks like a pouch or whatever, but they have the standard front opening, and that's all I really want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've tried my fair share of cotton options, and performance boxer briefs from Cory Vines (fine, except they don't breathe at all). In the interest of sharing information: reddit has a &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/8sivft/your_favorite_for_underpants/"&gt;megathread&lt;/a&gt;, and this guy did a &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/frugalmalefashion/comments/6piys2/the_ultimate_kinda_boxer_brief_review_saxx/?st=j62ixrd1&amp;amp;sh=4be40aaf"&gt;two&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/6s7w7e/the_ultimate_kinda_boxer_brief_review_part_2/"&gt;part&lt;/a&gt; roundup. But these are relatively new, so it's no surprise they&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The look is nothing special, but let's be honest, nobody's looking at my underwear anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Wool-Tie.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Wool-Tie-2.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Wool-Tie-Back.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions: Twillory Shirts and Underwear"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="bonuswoolherringbonetie"&gt;Bonus: Wool Herringbone Tie&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I actually got this tie years back, from the only Sprezzabox I ever got, which I paid a half-fee of $10 for. I wore the socks, and while the tie is definitely a great value for $10 &lt;em&gt;if you want it&lt;/em&gt;, I never really had a good reason to wear a wool tie. And that's why you shouldn't buy boxes! The tie is thick and pleasant to the hand, but I haven't even had the occasion to knot it yet...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'll find the right fit for this one of these days, but in the meantime, here's a photo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They don't seem to make this tie anymore, but I suppose it reflects something about the brand, and who doesn't like a few bonus photos!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Quarantine Sales</title><description>I wasn't planning on writing about sales very often, but there are a few going on right now that need to be noted.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/quarantine-sales/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e7557e1dc65ec34ae43348e</guid><category>sales</category><category>dress shoes</category><category>shoes</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 13:57:44 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Being-Happy.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Being-Happy.jpg" alt="Quarantine Sales"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wasn't planning on writing about sales very often, but there are a few going on right now that need to be noted. This, in addition to the fact that many of you are probably at home right now, bored, itching  to buy something, I figured I'd make a few good retail therapy recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that these are not especially cheap brands, but they offer good values all around, and rarely offer sales. Also note, in case you're curious, that there are no affiliate links or other incentives here -- I'm recommending them because they're cheap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So let's get to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="grantstone"&gt;Grant Stone&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.grantstoneshoes.com/"&gt;Grant Stone&lt;/a&gt; sells cool shoes, boots, and leather goods. Generally, they're on the casual end of what dress shoes are, which is a cool space to be in -- smarter and more interesting than sneakers, but not too sleek to wear with jeans or shorts or whatever. Known for boots, longwings and penny loafers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They're having a sitewide sale for... well, not for any particular amount, but every pair of shoes they sell is on sale, and they were all good values to begin with, so pick something you like and enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="skoaktiebolaget"&gt;Skoaktiebolaget&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know you're part of the menswear crowd when you can spell &amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://www.skoaktiebolaget.com/"&gt;Skoaktiebolaget&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; without looking it up. They sell high end shoes from multiple brands, as well as a few fancy accessories and shoe care products. Again, you'd have a hard time finding a bad deal here, even at regular prices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They're offering 25% off everything site wide, which is pretty crazy, as they usually only put odd stock on sale, and the brands they carry almost never have sales of their own. Use the code 25off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="nomanwalksalone"&gt;No Man Walks Alone&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nomanwalksalone.com/?SID=42e18mnleeav55mgjjj3003k86"&gt;No Man Walks Alone&lt;/a&gt; is a New York based menswear boutique that deals in a hundred awesome different brands. There's a pretty good variety of high end stuff there, and I'm not sure how to describe the casual vibe, so &lt;a href="https://nomanwalksalone.com/portfolio/fw-19-lookbook/"&gt;here's their look book with Alex Delaney from Bon Apetit&lt;/a&gt;. Yeah, that happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They do put things on sale occasionally, and they have a sample sale in NYC most years around late May / early June (ish). However, this is still a pretty great sale; you get 20% off all online orders with the code &amp;quot;staysafe,&amp;quot; plus they're donating 20% of their profits to Meals on Wheels' COVID-19 response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="supplyandadvise"&gt;Supply and Advise&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.supplyandadvise.com/"&gt;Supply and Advise&lt;/a&gt; is what happens when two great menswear shops crash into one another and explode into a mess of awesome. Their space in Miami is cool; the space downstairs reflects the &amp;quot;Supply&amp;quot; identity with a lot of military-inspired menswear, Engineered Garments, RRL, stuff like that. Go upstairs, and you see what they mean by &amp;quot;Advise.&amp;quot; Drake's, Ring Jacket, and 100 Hands, along with some great whiskey. Pepper in some Aldens, GBV, Sunspel, and, I don't know, everything else you want, and you've got a cool brand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So their spring sale gives you 20% off all that good stuff (with the code &amp;quot;spring&amp;quot;). Some of these brands might have gone on sale anyway, but you're not going to be disappointed with anything you get from here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're still interested, I wrote about them &lt;a href="https://dresscode.danhakimi.com/a-visit-to-supply/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, that's it for now. I'll update this article if I see one or two more noteworthy sales... And if I see a bunch, I'll point that out in some more obvious way. Until then -- feel free to reach out to me for TV recommendations, and stay safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City</title><description>Oh, the things we do to look good.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/a-visit-to-kent-wang-in-nyc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e5e64a167fc4412557573cf</guid><category>kent wang</category><category>store visit</category><category>pocket squares</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>menswear</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 15:26:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Rose-Window-Cover.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Rose-Window-Cover.jpg" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/"&gt;Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt; is an interesting brand. A favorite of /r/malefashionadvice for providing a great value, it comes -- as with any such brand -- with a few compromises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of those compromises is their retail space. If you've heard of people in NYC living in closets and shoeboxes, you might understand this. Kent Wang's &amp;quot;store&amp;quot; is only open two days a week, and only by appointment. It's not listed in its building's floor directory, so I had to call up to figure out what floor it's on -- I'm sorry to say that I've since forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A friendly salesman named Aaron opened the door, welcoming me into a room they share with another brand, separated by a divider -- the cheap kind, not the fake wall of a flex. And it's about the size of a larger-than-average walk-in closet. The floors are crude and unfinished, as you'll see, and there aren't too many places to sit. But I didn't mind, really. I wasn't there for the ambiance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, the things we do to look good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Pocket-Squares-1.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Pocket-Squares-2.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Pocket Squares&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/pocket-squares"&gt;pocket squares&lt;/a&gt; are a selling point for the brand. Although I only bought a plain white linen square myself ($20), I've often found myself enamored with their patterned squares (generally $45, generally silk). I'll close off this article with a few instagram posts showing them off -- something to look forward to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aaron actually offered to sell me his own Rose Window pocket square, since they didn't have a regular one in stock. That's a cool move, Aaron, even if you will just get another one for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Gloves-and-Cardigans.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Gloves and Knitwear&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/misc/gloves"&gt;gloves&lt;/a&gt; were also great. Deerskin with Cashmere Lining. Really solid option there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But then... The &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/outerwear/shawl-cardigan-cream.html"&gt;shawl cardigan&lt;/a&gt; (which is inexplicably in the outerwear section of their website). This is one of the pieces I really wanted to try out, but in person, it really didn't live up to my (admittedly high) expectations. It was a warmer, yellower tone than any of the photography showed. It was a full size smaller than you could reasonably expect -- definitely size up. And the material was itchy and just... not very pleasant. I guess it must break in. I'm sure some people would appreciate it, but it was not for me, so the main lesson here is just: Try things on before you buy them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Watches-Sunglasses-Chopsticks-1.jpg" width="1080" height="810" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Watches-Candles-1.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Watches, Sunglasses, Candles, and Chopsticks&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/misc/watches"&gt;Watches&lt;/a&gt;! I've had my eye on their Bauhaus watches (left) for a while. They're nice mechanical/automatic watches for $350-$400. Well-designed. The Art Deco watch (right, $450) is less my speed, but might be right for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/misc/sunglasses/sunglasses-keyhole.html"&gt;Keyhole Sunglasses&lt;/a&gt; ($55 for acetate, $150 for horn) are pretty cool. They're a point of pride for the brand, and at those prices, they really should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have candles and &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/misc/fragrance"&gt;fragrances&lt;/a&gt; from Jardin de France.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And they have thick &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/misc/dinnerware/ebony-chopsticks.html"&gt;ebony chopsticks&lt;/a&gt; at $5 a pair. I almost bought two, but this was their only pair in stock, and I was looking for a set I could share with a guest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Dress-Shoes.jpg" width="1080" height="810" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Sneakers.jpg" width="1080" height="810" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Dress shoes and sneakers. NOte the stain on the right side of the floor. They're not focusing on presentation here. They're banking on the theory that quality speaks for itself.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dress shoes seemed pretty nice at a glance. Some cool antiquing effects. The sneakers were nice too, although rumor has it that they come with the stink of a thousand leather goods, and retain that stink for months, so I'm looking elsewhere for sneakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Fabric-Books.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Fabric books&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;And here's a great reason to go in person: they have an extremely large number of fabrics and linings to choose from. Like, more than you see here. A huge portion of their office is just piles and piles of fabric books for your perusal. On top of the old standards, I really enjoyed the Drago fabrics. Their lining options didn't just include the standard solid bembergs, but a variety of materials, subtle patterns, wacky patterns, cultural references, pieces of art, you name it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another customer was there with me -- I was there early, and his appointment ran long -- and I heard him going over his options. They offer way more customization than other MTM shops. A few stood out -- I believe they mentioned four different pocket width options, which... I can see why I would want that, but I might not ever have thought to ask. So that was pretty exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They do fully canvassed MTM suits and half canvassed outerwear at great prices. But you &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to go in person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Mannequin.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="A Visit to Kent Wang in New York City"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Grenadines!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;They have &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/ties/grenadine"&gt;Grenadine Ties&lt;/a&gt; for $75. Grenadine ties are a really cool weave that provides texture that can make a solid color interesting. They also have &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/ties/ancient-madder"&gt;Ancient Madders&lt;/a&gt; for $75 and &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/ties/six-fold"&gt;Sixfold Ties&lt;/a&gt; for $85. These are more really solid prices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're curious to learn more about the brand, consider reading Kent's &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/e8cmw7/ama_with_kent_wang_menswear_designer_of/"&gt;AMA on reddit&lt;/a&gt;. Now, get ready for some funky squares.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B5prUCwpOm_/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B5prUCwpOm_/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B5prUCwpOm_/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;You can only pick one for your next outfit, which are you going with? 🤔 . 🔢 Edo Castle, Norte Dame rose window, The Hunt of the Unicorn, or East Indies Ortelius pocket square. . . . #kentwang #pocketsquare #pocketsquares #rakish #rakishgent #gentlemenstyle #classicmenswear #stylishmen #menstailoring #stylishgent #sartorial #madetobeworn #styleforum #dandystyle #mnswr #ptoman #mensweardaily #menswearblog #mensjackets #dapper #dappered #sprezzatura #menstyle #mensfashion #menswear #menwithclass #menwithstyle #ootdmen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kent.wang/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt; (@kent.wang) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-12-04T12:53:03+00:00"&gt;Dec 4, 2019 at 4:53am PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bxu0ueJAgtf/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bxu0ueJAgtf/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bxu0ueJAgtf/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;Star chart Burritt white pocket square from artist Elijah Burritt. . First published in 1833, this star chart depicts the northern circumpolar constellations for each month of the year. The depicted constellations are also shown in the center of the Star chart Cellarius, in particular Ursa Major, the bear, and Camelopardalis, the giraffe. Also available with a navy background. . . . #kentwang #pocketsquares #pocketsquare #rakish #rakishgent #gentlemenstyle #classicmenswear #stylishmen #menstailoring #stylishgent #sartorial #madetobeworn #styleforum #dandystyle #mnswr #ptoman #mensweardaily #dapper #dappered #sprezzatura #style #stylish #fashion #menstyle #mensfashion #menswear #menwithclass #menwithstyle #ootdmen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kent.wang/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt; (@kent.wang) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-05-21T16:40:21+00:00"&gt;May 21, 2019 at 9:40am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3o10PcJLMo/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3o10PcJLMo/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3o10PcJLMo/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;Dendera zodiac pocket square. . The Dendera zodiac is a bas-relief ceiling from the temple of Hathor in Dendera, Egypt. Based on the position of the stars, paleoastronomers have determined that it dates from 30 BC–30 AD, during the Late Period of ancient Egypt. Both Mesopotamian and Egyptian sky iconography are elegantly combined in the composition. . The central disc represents the celestial realm which include Ursa Major, the great bear, and Tauret, the pregnant hippo-lion goddess. Another ring of figures outside of these circumpolar star groups depict Greco-Roman astrological signs such as the Ram, Lion, Bull, and Scorpion. Around the rim of the sky disc, Decans or &amp;#39;hour stars&amp;#39; used to track time appear above the horizon at dawn. Outside of the sky disc, four pairs of falcon-headed gods and four priestesses from the Temple of Isis are shown holding the heavens above the earth. . The Dendera zodiac is on display at the Louvre Museum in Paris, and has lost its original painted decoration. Ken Bakeman has researched and meticulously redrawn the design, adding color in keeping with the vision of the original Egyptian artists. . . . #kentwang #pocketsquare #pocketsquares #rakish #rakishgent #gentlemenstyle #classicmenswear #stylishmen #menstailoring #stylishgent #sartorial #madetobeworn #styleforum #dandystyle #mnswr #ptoman #mensweardaily #mensjackets #dapper #dappered #sprezzatura #style #stylish #fashion #menstyle #mensfashion #menswear #menwithclass #menwithstyle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kent.wang/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt; (@kent.wang) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-10-15T12:02:48+00:00"&gt;Oct 15, 2019 at 5:02am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6NvV1vJfQw/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6NvV1vJfQw/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6NvV1vJfQw/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;Rickshaw Cart pocket square. . Illustrated by Jed Henry as part of his Ukiyo-e Heroes series. . The top cartouche phonetically reads &amp;#34;Ma-ri-o&amp;#34;, and the bottom cartouche means &amp;#34;Beloved friends, dear rivals&amp;#34;. . The design of Bowser is based on the legendary dragon turtle from Chinese mythology, a chimeric creature with the body of a turtle and the head of a dragon. Later period ukiyo-e artists such Utagawa Kuniyoshi often depicted such monsters and anthropomorphic creatures in their fantastical woodblock prints. Jed now brings this millennia-old motif full circle by merging 19th century Japanese woodblocks with 20th century video games. . Swipe for a full look at the design. . . . #kentwang #rakish #pocketsquare #pocketsquares #rakishgent #gentlemenstyle #classicmenswear #stylishmen #menstailoring #stylishgent #sartorial #madetobeworn #styleforum #dandystyle #mnswr #ptoman #mensweardaily #dapper #dappered #sprezzatura #style #menstyle #mensfashion #menswear #menwithclass #menwithstyle #ootdmen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/kent.wang/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt; (@kent.wang) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-12-18T13:00:54+00:00"&gt;Dec 18, 2019 at 5:00am PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat</title><description>This coat is... not especially good.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/initial-impressions-vintage-brooks-brothers-tie-asket-shirt/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e5be50a67fc441255757282</guid><category>impressions</category><category>neckwear</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>menswear</category><category>asket</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Peacoat-and-Tie-Cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Asket-Shirt-1.jpg" width="1080" height="1441" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Asket-Shirt-2.jpg" width="1080" height="810" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Pictured here with the wrong shoes (left) and fresh out the box (right). Yes, I know the collar looks flat on the right – it popped up nice and fast. I'll get you better photos after I have it tailored.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="1oxfordshirtfromasket"&gt;1. Oxford Shirt from Asket&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Peacoat-and-Tie-Cover-1.jpg" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brand: Asket&lt;br&gt;
Item: &lt;a href="https://www.asket.com/shop/shirts/oxford-shirt-white"&gt;Oxford Shirt, White&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Size: Medium Short&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that I received this shirt at no cost in consideration of my review. Regular price for this shirt is $105.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like it! It's a nice oxford -- a little stiff for now. but it'll soften up over time. It weighs in at 175gsm, which, as I understand it, is substantial but not heavy for an oxford. The collar roll is not especially intense, but that's just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of details, we have a back center pleat and a button on the back of the collar. The buttons are Mother of Pearl,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hem is good for wearing untucked, which is good, because it comes in a short length!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of the length -- the sleeves aren't quite short enough for me, and while fit is personal, this brings up one issue with these shirts... At $105 US, they're competing with Made to Measure shirting. I'm really excited to have a shirt that fits me relatively well off the rack, and it's definitely a nice shirt, but if I factor in tailoring, it's &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; expensive than made to measure options, and that's a tough pill to swallow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to mention, again -- although I imagine many of you have heard me talk about it by now -- that Asket is a super ethical brand. They offer traceability and transparency into their processes, so you can understand, better than with most companies, just how they treat their workers and how sustainable their practices are. They promote proper garment care, and use minimal packaging, and do a lot of other little things that really signal their intent to be good corporate citizens. That's worth a few points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full review to come after I've had it tailored and actually worn it well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Vintage-Brooks-Brothers-Tie-3.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Vintage-Brooks-Brothers-Tie-1.jpg" width="1080" height="1175" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Vintage-Brooks-Brothers-Tie-2.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This tie is unreasonably difficult to capture on camera. Although the colors look relatively good in these photos... Honestly, none of them do it justice.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="2vintagebrooksbrothersancientmadderpaisleytiefromluxeswap"&gt;2. Vintage Brooks Brothers Ancient Madder Paisley Tie from LuxeSwap&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brand: Brooks Brothers&lt;br&gt;
Purchased on auction from &lt;a href="https://www.ebay.com/sch/balearic1/m.html?_nkw=&amp;amp;_armrs=1&amp;amp;_ipg=&amp;amp;_from="&gt;Luxeswap on eBay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love this tie. The colors are beautiful and hard to capture on camera. There's not too much to review, but there's plenty to talk about...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's untipped. In case you don't know what that means... A tie has two kinds of lining. The first is the interlining, which is the thickish stuff in the middle of the tie that isn't just a thin layer of silk, which allows you to tie  it without crushing it and get a decent knot. The second is regular lining -- &amp;quot;untipped&amp;quot; means it does not have that lining, so if you look at the back tip of the tie, you just see the same layer of fabric on the front, and it's super light.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And it's an ancient madder. And again, in case you don't know what that means: madder is a type of dye that creates really cool colors, but silk doesn't normally take very nicely to it... Unless you strip the natural coating from the silk, dye it in that raw form, and coat it again with gum arabic, creating a unique look and feel. Not a lot of brands still do this, so the effect is pretty unique and special. You might have to see one of these in person to really appreciate the depth of the colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buying vintage accessories is cool. Aside from being super sustainable, good vintage clothing can be very well-made. And with accessories, there's relatively little risk that you get something that  This one is a little short, but it's well made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally... &lt;a href="https://www.ebay.com/sch/balearic1/m.html?_nkw=&amp;amp;_armrs=1&amp;amp;_ipg=&amp;amp;_from="&gt;Luxeswap&lt;/a&gt;! You should buy things from Luxeswap. They auction off high-end menswear, and while many well-dressed men know about them, their auction prices still often end up being better than the prices you'd find on Grailed or TheRealReal. Just remember: patience is a virtue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Saks-Peacoat-1.jpg" width="1080" height="1440" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/03/Saks-Peacoat-Details-1.jpg" width="1080" height="810" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected: Asket OCBD, Vintage Brooks Brothers Tie, Saks Pea Coat"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Again, I struggled to capture the color here. But here, it's because the color is constantly changing in person. Sometimes it's redder, sometimes it's purpler, sometimes it's even a little brownish.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="3saksfifthavenuepeacoat"&gt;3. Saks Fifth Avenue Pea Coat&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand&lt;/strong&gt;: Saks Fifth Avenue&lt;br&gt;
Purchased for $95 from a Prive / Brunello Cucinelli sample sale. No materials tag or size tag or anything.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Color&lt;/strong&gt;: Idk, purpleish? Burgunplum? Red Wine Sangria? It changes colors in different lighting, come up with your own names for it and @ me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This coat is... not especially good. Barely any lining, which means it's not very warm. And the fabric... isn't bad, but I suspect there's some polyamide or something else other than wool in here. Machined buttonholes, including a sealed lapel buttonhole. Non-functional buttonholes on the arm. The buttons are thick and colorful, but they might be acetate or something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On top of that... It doesn't fit especially well. It's a size big in every dimension I can fit a blazer under it, which, for a pea coat, is kind of incorrect -- pea coats are relatively casual. I can wear a thick cardigan under it too, or just accept that it's a loose fit, but there's nothing fantastic about the drape either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I love the color. And I wanted something double breasted to play with. And for $95... this thing is fine. I'll wear it through a good chunk of spring, and probably keep wearing it over superior outerwear just because of the color. Which kinda goes to show you... if it looks good, it looks good, and the abstract ideal of quality doesn't always need to override that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For reference, I think it's &lt;a href="https://www.saksfifthavenue.com/saks-fifth-avenue-collection-double-breasted-peacoat/product/0400011154846"&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;, but in a different color. Don't buy it at that price. The fact that they don't state material percentages worries me a bit... But I'll survive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the way -- sneak preview! -- I have four items from Twillory sitting in my closet, so they're going to get their own post soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Your Guide to Leap Day 2020</title><description>You know the saying -- "Rhubarb red, eat away; rhubarb green, don't eat them!"</description><link>http://localhost:2368/your-guide-to-leap-day-2020/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e037f382bcaeb297fdb8d1e</guid><category>humor</category><category>holidays</category><category>fun</category><category>guide</category><category>30 rock</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 15:56:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/Leap-Dave-Williams.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/Leap-Dave-Williams.jpg" alt="Your Guide to Leap Day 2020"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ah, Leap Day! The most fantastical unbelievable ridiculous holiday of the four-ish-year-cycle. And one of the biggest fashion opportunities of the year! While you're munching away at your rhubarb, consider these trends and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="general-principles"&gt;General Principles&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;First, and most important, &lt;strong&gt;nothing that happens on Leap Day counts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;That means you can spend as much money as you want, and, legally, your credit card company can't make you pay it off. (This is not legal advice).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This also means that you can dress in the most ridiculous bullshit you can think of, and, if it doesn't look good, oh well! It's Leap Day! Real life is for March!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leap Day is usually cold, so you'll generally want to layer up in warm clothing. Or not, it's Leap Day, do whatever you want.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Finally -- and this should be obvious -- wear blue and yellow, unless you want to get poked in the eye.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;So -- we're looking for loud, expensive pieces you've been wanting for the past four years, ideally in blue and yellow. Let's take a leap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="inspiration"&gt;Inspiration&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can start by checking out &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/YCx44os"&gt;this great color combo album&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HalfTheGoldTreasure"&gt;/u/halfthegoldtreasure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Film Inspiration, you would be well-off watching Leap Dave Williams 2: Leap Baby, which despite coming out in 2012, is a major menswear upgrade from the original. This year's Leap Day also looks promising, even for a rom com, but it's obviously not out yet, so we'll see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 id="tops"&gt;Tops&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.chadprom.com/product/ribbed-turtleneck-mustard/167/?cate_no=45&amp;amp;display_group=1"&gt;Chad Prom Ribbed Turtleneck in Mustard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/70kdDlK"&gt;Loro Piana Baby Cashmere&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/loro-piana/knitted-zip-throughs/cable-knit-baby-cashmere-half-zip-sweater/9679066508504527"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;). You know what they say, "oh my fucking God it's baby cashmere!"&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.drakes.com/clothing/knitwear/drake-s-x-aime-leon-dore-blue-and-gold-block-stripe-jumper"&gt;Drake's x Aimé Leon Dore Blue and Gold Block Stripe Jumper&lt;/a&gt; -- on the cheaper side of their offerings, but very appropriate to the theme.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nomanwalksalone.com/clothing/relaxed-blazer-in-mustard-yellow-cotton-and-linen.html"&gt;Document Blazer&lt;/a&gt; in yellow.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://shop.ringjacket.com/products/navy-balloon-jacket"&gt;The Ring Jacket Balloon Jacket&lt;/a&gt; looks like your run-of-the-mill nice navy blazer on the surface, but, in fact, it's an &lt;em&gt;extremely nice&lt;/em&gt; navy blazer, and comfortable to the point where it's downright weird for a blazer to be this comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thearmoury.com/collections/knitwear/products/the-armoury-merino-wool-sleeveless-cardigan?variant=30247796932679"&gt;The Armoury Sweater Vest&lt;/a&gt;, a good layer for a Leap Day William costume.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1 id="bottoms"&gt;Bottoms&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.marianorubinacci.net/manny-jeans?path=64"&gt;A proper pair of trousers from Rubinacci that just happen to be made of denim.&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://18east.co/collections/leon-washere-for-18-east/products/waterbury-fleece-pant-petrol"&gt;18 East Waterbury Fleece Pants in Balsam Blue&lt;/a&gt;. My first of two pairs from this brand, a great one to look at for funky pants in general.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6Wlr38pTO-/"&gt;18 East Yellow Cable-Cord Single Pleat Pants&lt;/a&gt;. Yellow is a loud color, and difficult to wear. Don't you want to try it with some fly-ass wide corduroys?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://nomanwalksalone.com/clothing/plain-turtle-16-swim-trunks-artisan-gold.html"&gt;Lightning Bolt Swim Trunks&lt;/a&gt;, if you're taking a Leap Day vacation this year. I recommend Indonesia -- they do leap day &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thearmoury.com/collections/trousers/products/ring-jacket-amp03-cotton-trousers?variant=39517152271"&gt;The Armoury x Ring Jacket Model A trousers&lt;/a&gt;, available in a variety of ridiculous colors.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1 id="outerwear"&gt;Outerwear&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/KmD9Yd6"&gt;Gucci Oversized Quilted Logo-Jacquard Shell Hooded Down Jacket&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/gucci/down-jackets/oversized-quilted-logo-jacquard-shell-hooded-down-jacket/990541377579025"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;) -- blue, yellow, loud, warm &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; expensive, all in one garment!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/7xDoYG7"&gt;Fear of God Appliquéd Suede-Panelled Faux Suede Bomber Jacket&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/fear-of-god/bomber-jackets/appliqued-suede-panelled-faux-suede-bomber-jacket/5983760398340571"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;), because you can afford to spend $1800 but not even get real suede.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/7RkwGpr"&gt;Navy Suede Valstarino&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/valstar/clothing/leather-jackets/valstarino-slim-fit-suede-bomber-jacket/10802260992140564"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;) -- basic, for the cowards in the audience. Incidentally, a favorite of mine...&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1 id="footwear"&gt;Footwear&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/shoes/dover-navy-suede-handsewn-202-last.html"&gt;Edward Green Dovers&lt;/a&gt;, for you poors who can't afford bespoke footwear.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Nike-LDWaffle-Sacai/dp/B07SLL1K4V"&gt;Sacai Nike waffle runners&lt;/a&gt;. Huh, that's an Amazon link. Didn't see that one coming.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pntrac.com/t/Qz9LREJFP0RCREtESj9LREJF?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.koio.co%2Fproducts%2Ftempo-saffron-men"&gt;Koio Tempo Saffron&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.koio.co/collections/collection-men/products/tempo-saffron-men?variant=31105643937828"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.johnlobb.com/en_us/mens-shoes/foundry-rubber-sole-12990#selection.color=Blue%20White%20Orange%20Cross%20Grain%2FSuede%2FTechno%20Fabric"&gt;John Lobb Foundry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1 id="accessories"&gt;Accessories&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.drakes.com/ties/navy-orange-and-pink-boteh-print-silk-tie"&gt;This Somewhat Ridiculous Tie from Drake's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hermes.com/us/en/product/reve-de-mecanique-elementaire-scarf-65-H283392Tv26/"&gt;Hermès "Reve de Mecanique Elementaire scarf 65"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rolex.com/watches/day-date/m228348rbr-0002.html"&gt;Rolex Day-Date&lt;/a&gt; Gold is a kind of yellow, right?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/rGxjOJ6"&gt;Luis Morais bracelet&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/luis-morais/accessories/bracelets/14-karat-gold-diamond-bracelet/666467151984010"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://thearmoury.com/collections/gloves/products/hestra-elk-winston-handsewn-cashmere-lined-gloves?variant=1817948356623"&gt;Elk Winston Handsewn Cashmere-lined Gloves from Hestra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h1 id="sleepwear"&gt;Sleepwear&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a final suggestion -- start and end your day with &lt;a href="https://prf.hn/l/K3BGYA6"&gt;a nice robe from Derek Rose&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.mrporter.com/en-us/mens/product/derek-rose/clothing/robes/bailey-piped-silk-robe/5432698981498388"&gt;non-tracking link&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/Leap-Day-Kenneth.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Your Guide to Leap Day 2020"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h1 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the depths of the Marianas Trench all the way to Rockefeller Plaza, everybody who isn't Amish loves to celebrate Leap Day. Whether you're crying for candy or dining at Plunder, you should look your best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all, as Jim Carrey stated in is Oscar-nominated role as Leap Dave Willams, "&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MebXpWd__5w"&gt;I definitely don't have gills&lt;/a&gt;!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Merry Leap Day!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square</title><description>Initial impressions about three cool new things I got recently.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/initial-impressions-collected-delugs-watch-strap/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e3035e967fc441255757029</guid><category>casual</category><category>watches</category><category>impressions</category><category>reviews</category><category>tees</category><category>pocket squares</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/stack-angle-cover.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/strap-1-1.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/strap-back.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/strap-2.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/strap-on-wrist-1.jpg" width="900" height="901" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/strap-attacheroonies.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="1delugswatchstrapinnavyshellcordovan"&gt;1. Delugs Watch Strap in Navy Shell Cordovan&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/stack-angle-cover.jpg" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://delugs.com/"&gt;Delugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://delugs.com/collections/shell-cordovan-signature/products/navy-shell-cordovan-signature-watch-strap"&gt;Navy Shell Cordovan&lt;/a&gt; from Shinki Hikaku&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: Small length, 20mm lug width&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Customizations&lt;/strong&gt;: White Contrast Stitching&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Price Paid&lt;/strong&gt;: $80 shipped (Black Friday sale)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I can get a good leather belt from Meermin for $50. So I told myself, I should be able to find a quality leather watch strap that isn't &lt;em&gt;super&lt;/em&gt; casual for less than that, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, wrong. After a lot of searching, I came to a realization. The materials don't really cost anything. It's just the labor you're paying for, and stitching a watch strap well takes mroe labor than putting a belt together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delugs offers a ton of customization. By default, you can select length of both sides and lug width, but you can write your own sizes in, and request contrast stitching. They offer a lot of different kinds of leathers, including weird stuff like stingray. They also have those metal slidey things that make it easy to attach and detach the straps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like this one. I'm no expert on watch straps, and while I'm starting to suspect the white stitching makes it more casual than I was hoping, it still looks great to my eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's worth noting that the man behind the brand is pretty great. He's super responsive on Instagram and actually let me make a modification there after ordering, but before he started work on it. It did take more than a month, but that was understandable -- he sold a lot during his black friday sale, and he works alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strap was a little stiff when I got it, but it softened up nicely in just a few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/tee-fit-pic.jpg" width="900" height="1199" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/tee.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/navy-on-navy-on-navy.jpg" width="900" height="899" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="2askettshirtinnavy"&gt;2. Asket T-Shirt in Navy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.asket.com/"&gt;Asket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Item&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.asket.com/shop/t-shirts/t-shirt-dark-navy"&gt;T-Shirt, Navy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: Medium Short&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that I received this T-shirt at no cost in consideration of my review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clothing is, basically, one gigantic environmental disaster. And they say sunlight is the best disinfectant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So this tee is nice. I don't want to be a $45-tee kind of guy, but it is definitely a significant upgrade from my Uniqlo Supima Cotton tee. But I'll discuss that more specifically in the full review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But for now, it's really worth noting the premise of this brand. Asket doesn't just make quality basics. Asket does it &lt;em&gt;ethically&lt;/em&gt;. Now, I don't normally like to talk about ethics in menswear, because it's usually a flood of marketing jargon, greenwashing, and an occasional side of xenophobia. Asket isn't about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asket provides as much traceability and price transparency as it can. For the T-Shirt, that's only 68% traceability -- still a far cry better than most brands -- but they aspire to 100%, and get closer with items like their &lt;a href="https://www.asket.com/shop/shirts/oxford-shirt-white"&gt;Oxford Shirt&lt;/a&gt; (86% traceable). And they tell you where everything came from and where everything was made. Not just the shirt fabric, but the threads used to make the hem, neck, and armholes, and the polyester used to make the brand and materials tags. That's pretty hardcore. They also tell you what it cost them. Now, $45 for a tee shirt that cost $13 to make might not be &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; exciting (it's probably the kind of markup many brands charge on sale), but the transparency is. (I also think the &amp;quot;traditional retail&amp;quot; estimate is a little bit of a marketing shenanigan, but I'll indulge them that).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why is this transparency so great? Because it allows you to make real, informed decisions about the environmental and human impact of your purchase. And it helps us make sure that they don't use slave labor, which, in 2020, is an unreasonably common and complex problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also do a lot of other small things. Like small/minimal packaging (but not so tight as to make the tee shirt wrinkle, the lines smoothed out pretty easy for me). And their whole collection being full of basics means none of their stock ever has to sit dead in a warehouse -- nothing goes to waste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On top of that, they put a stress on proper &lt;a href="https://www.asket.com/garment-care/"&gt;garment care&lt;/a&gt;. They offer garment brushes and delicate detergents. They want your clothing to last, even though that means fewer sales for them -- because the best thing for the environment is to buy less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One last thing I want to restate -- they have short and long sizes! I don't like to review fit, since it's very specifically personal, but you can't complain about additional options. Very few brands offer tall and short sizes, and Bonobos' quality isn't anything to write home about, so if you're a tricky fit, get excited!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/square-1.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/square-size-1.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Watch for scale&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="3kentwangwhitelinenpocketsquare"&gt;3. Kent Wang White Linen Pocket Square&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.kentwang.com/pocket-squares/linen/linen-white.html"&gt;Kent Wang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Material&lt;/strong&gt;: Linen&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Price&lt;/strong&gt;: $20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, it's not just a linen pocket square... It's a nice one. Soft. Pleasant. Bigger than I expected. I feel like I've read somewhere that the difference between a pocket square and handkercheif is size, but I feel like I'll hate myself a little bit more if I look that up, so... It's a big pocket square. There's got to be a limit to my fashion nerding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Linen is a voluminous material, and given the size of this thing, even a TV fold (the boring one) takes up some space in your pocket. If your jacket is slim in the chest, this might actually affect fit, drape, and symmetry. So be careful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For what it's worth, their other linen squares seemed smaller, and the silk ones are definitely safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/02/stack-straight.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Initial Impressions, Collected -- Delugs Watch Strap, Asket Tee Shirt, Kent Wang Pocket Square"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review</title><description>This is equal parts review and love letter. Unfortunately, you can't buy these shoes -- but you can buy other Meermins, and you should.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/meermin-mallorca-horsebit-loafers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e23c13055327f1bff4c2573</guid><category>reviews</category><category>meermin</category><category>bit loafers</category><category>loafers</category><category>dress shoes</category><category>shoes</category><category>menswear</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 22:13:23 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-2-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Suit.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Yes, I can wear these with a suit – although some edge dressing might have been a good idea.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="quickstats"&gt;Quick Stats&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-2-1.jpg" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note: These are &lt;strong&gt;seconds&lt;/strong&gt;, purchased from Meermin's &lt;a href="https://www.ebay.com/usr/goodyearshoes?_trksid=p2053788.m1543.l2754"&gt;eBay Store&lt;/a&gt;. These have, somewhere, fallen short of Meermin's QC standards. But I'm not sure I know where.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brand&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://meermin.com/"&gt;Meermin Mallorca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: 6.5 UK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Last&lt;/strong&gt;: Beat (you haven't heard of this last. I'll get into that).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Color&lt;/strong&gt;: Dark Brown&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Soles&lt;/strong&gt;: Leather&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Construction&lt;/strong&gt;: Goodyear Welt, Moccasin-style Lasting&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Horsebit&lt;/strong&gt;: Nickel&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Price&lt;/strong&gt;: $95 shipped for seconds at acution. Presumably $195 + shipping if they were firsts, although they can no longer be purcased. Yes, I know, I know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The box contained the shoes and one dust bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="buyingprocess"&gt;Buying Process&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meermin's seconds store is a strange place. They ship from Spain, and that costs $35. And their shoes, belts, and wallets are very reasonably priced to begin with. So you have to bid unreasonably low numbers to actually get a deal -- if you bid, say, $120, which you might say is roughly the right price for a pair of Meermin seconds, you'll find yourself paying $155, at which point you might as well go to their NYC store and buy firsts. It's stranger with belts: bidding starts at $10, and first belts go for $50 without tax in state, so if you bid more than $15, you're overpaying! And auctions last 3 days, so you don't have much time to decide how much you want the pair you see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I swear, I've seen people pay more for Meermin seconds than firsts. So I spent quite some time looking through the store at my small size, often making lowball bids. Eventually, I fell ass-backwards into this pair. I knew they were bit loafers, but didn't really understand the history behind them, moccasin construction, or anything like that. But after I won my first pair of Meermins... Boy, did I get into some research. That's about the time I wrote &lt;a href="https://dresscode.danhakimi.com/how-to-talk-about-loafers/"&gt;How to Talk About Loafers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They took a couple of weeks to ship from Spain. Patience is a virtue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that, for normal purchases, Meermin's returns process is not especially friendly, so it's always better to buy in store, or at least try on your size in store. Otherwise, you'll probably be on the hook for shipping each way. That's not ideal. As a general tip -- my size is a 6.5 US in some lasts, and a 7uk in others. I usually wear about a 7.5 US in most dress shoes. But my feeet are strange, and guessing is never a great idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="whattheylookedlikenew"&gt;What they looked like new&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Initial-Impressions-1-3.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Initial-Impressions-2-2.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Initial-Impressions-3-2.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Wait, these were seconds?&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, sometimes, people have trouble understanding why a pair of seconds are seconds. What is wrong with these shoes? Nothing I could spot. The seam around the front strikes me as more &amp;quot;imperfect because it's handmade&amp;quot; than &amp;quot;unbecoming of a proper shoe brand.&amp;quot; Maybe I'm just not picky enough, but I couldn't figure out the problem. So score one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And they fit! I had never tried on the beat last -- it doesn't entirely exist, and the Meermin store in NYC hadn't opened yet -- so... They were on the tight side, but I had to celebrate this fact. They fit!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="breakingthemin"&gt;Breaking Them In&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meermin has a notorious break in period, and, again, these were on the tight side. It doesn't help that I once attended to wear them with a pair of no-show socks that was just a little too-low-cut -- that was a painful learning experience. But eventually, the break-in was over, and now, I can safely say that these are comfortable-ish. I mean, they won't win any comfortable awards, but I'm not opposed to putting them on, and for a dress shoe at this price tier, that's a win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="oneofsomesmallnumber"&gt;One of... Some small number.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You've never seen these, before, have you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you heard of Meermin's Beat last? Can you find info about it... anywhere? The searches I run only seem to result in posts I've made, so if anybody else has gotten a pair of these, that person is not the type to write about them online. At least not in English.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don't know, a &amp;quot;last&amp;quot; is basically the thing that gives the shoe its shape. For those who knew that: the Beat last is a little different. Normally, a shoe is lasted by stretching the leather over the last into the shape of a shoe's upper. But the Beat last is a moccasin last, and moccasins are lasted differently. The leather is stretched up from the bottom, and sewn at that big chunky seam you see, cradling the foot in a soft, round layer of leather. Native Americans wore shoes made like this as soft-soled moccasins to move through forests easily. Then Aurland Shoes came and threw on a rigid sole and heel, transforming the moccasin into one of the first ever loafers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moccasin-style loafers are usually more casual, but for reasons I get into in &lt;a href="https://dresscode.danhakimi.com/how-to-talk-about-loafers/"&gt;How to Talk About Loafers&lt;/a&gt;, the moccasin-style horsebit loafer is unusually versatile, valid even with a suit. They contrast starkly with the &lt;a href="https://meermin.com/in_en/10167010190000se-19-101670-black-calf-e-negro.html"&gt;apron toe loafers here&lt;/a&gt;, which, despite the relatively thick handsewn seam, are relatively sleek, and almost feminine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These shoes were apparently once available on Meermin's website, but as far as I'm concerned, they're one of one. And you can get an MTO, but short of going bespoke, you don't have a shoe with a unique last. And I do. That's really cool. (If you have a pair of shoes in this last, please reach out -- we'll start a club).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, this makes this review a little silly. You can't buy these shoes, or anything like them to the point where telling you how great they are is useful. I can tell you that Meermin is a great company selling great shoes for a great price... But they're not selling these. Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="review"&gt;Review&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-2.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-1.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-3.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-5.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Review-4.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, as you've probably gathered by now... I like these shoes. I'm very happy with them. I've come into the horsebit loafer style -- I think of them as statement pieces, but they are also the traditional footwear of the land I come from -- the West Egg of Long Island, now home of my Persian brethren.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relax, I'm not wearing these with an Hermes belt or an unearned belief that everybody I meet has seen the face of God. But I am wearing them every-which way I can. With cropped chinos, with a suit, with shorts. With boring dress socks, with fun ones, with no-shows. To work, to bars, to house parties. With brown, and with gray. Yes, they were part of the inspiration for the first piece I wrote for this blog: &lt;a href="https://dresscode.danhakimi.com/versatile-but-not-minimal/"&gt;Versatile, but not Minimal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And they're compliment-getters. Whether I'm out in the real world or home in Great Neck, these things grab the eye and earn that attention the right way. I'm happy for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The color is a mid-dark brown, with some reddish tones in the right lighting. The bit is nickel, which I find much more palatable than the usually garish gold tones. I'm not sure how I'll maintain the metal long term -- any tips on that would be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for comfort: the soles are not especially flexible -- a limitation of the goodyear welt -- but they're fine. The uppers are not especially soft -- not compared to my more expensive J. FitzPatricks, at least, they compare favorably to everything else in my closet -- but for $200, they're really fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, better than fine. Take a look at the photos. I've had these shoes for about 22 months. And while I haven't worn them &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; many times, I haven't babied them either. You can barely tell, from the uppers, that they've been worn. I haven't even bothered to polish them yet, because... Again, aside from some edge dressing, they don't need it. They've been brushed on occasion and conditioned a few times, but have otherwise gotten no special treatment. The soles have weathered a few long days in and around New York City, including rainy days (when I was afraid to wear some other shoes that would not have held up as well).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can read more about Meermin's quality construction and materials elsewhere. You'll read very good things. These shoes will last me a lifetime with a small number of resoles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So... I like these shoes. Would I pay full price for them now? Probably, yeah. Would I recommend Meermin at $195? This is not a proper hypothetical -- I recommend them constantly, on reddit and to my friends in person. A few have taken me up on it. One friend spoke highly of them ater break in, before he regressed to Cole Haan, citing comfort concerns, but remember that Cole Haan glues poor leather uppers to poor soles to make generally ugly and overpriced shoes. Another saves his tan wholecuts for when he needs a compliment -- and they, too, deliver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="conclusion"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, for those who are skimming: I'm very happy with these shoes, and would wholeheartedly recommend future purchases from Meermin. They use great leather and quality construction to deliver quality dress shoes at a remarkably low price. They're not especially comfortable, but after a break-in, they're about what you'd expect. The styling on this pair, as with most shoes they make, is quite nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would recommend care in sizing, particularly if you cannot get to their store, but I'd generally recommend that no matter who you're buying from. It's just slightly more noteworthy here due to the shipping expense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a reminder, I won these shoes at auction. I have no relationship with Meermin, aside from occasional visits to their store and compliments paid to the employees working there. I'm only telling you good things because I think those things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now go out there and get yourself a pair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Shorts-1.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Shorts-2.jpg" width="900" height="675" alt="Meermin Mallorca Horsebit Loafer Review"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;I should hit the gym...&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="alternatives"&gt;Alternatives&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, I'm sorry to be telling you about something you can't buy. But here are some alternatives!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apron toe -- more common, sleeker, sometimes feminine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://meermin.com/in_en/10167010190000se-19-101670-black-calf-e-negro.html"&gt;Meermin Hiro Last&lt;/a&gt; (or Made to Order -- you might get them to recreate this shoe if they still have the beat last on hand)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jfitzpatrickfootwear.com/collections/boutique/products/pike-copper-museum-calf-presale"&gt;J. FitzPatrick Pike&lt;/a&gt; -- currently on sale for a steal at $295. Let him know Dan Hakimi sent you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/mens-loafers/horsebit-loafers-navy-cordovan-80643"&gt;Carmina Uetam Last&lt;/a&gt; -- this pair is in navy shell, so it's a little more expensive, but they make cheaper ones too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moc Toe -- less common, uniquely versatile, not sleek at all&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;GH Bass (&lt;a href="https://www.pntrs.com/t/Qz9JREZHP0RCREtESj9JREZH?website=308802&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ghbass.com%2Fproduct%2Flincoln%2Beasy%2Bweejuns.do%3Flocale%3Dus"&gt;Affiliate Link&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="https://www.ghbass.com/product/lincoln+easy+weejuns.do?selectedOption=567924"&gt;Regular Link&lt;/a&gt;) -- not exactly quality footwear (unimpressive leather, cemented soles), but they look good enough, have a pretty rich history, and can be found on sale. A good way to test out the style.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beckett Simonon Beaumont (&lt;a href="https://www.beckettsimonon.com/products/beaumont-horsebit-loafers?rfsn=3353795.2c9040&amp;amp;utm_source=refersion&amp;amp;utm_campaign=affiliate&amp;amp;variant=29707534336079"&gt;Referral Link&lt;/a&gt;|&lt;a href="https://www.beckettsimonon.com/products/beaumont-horsebit-loafers?variant=29707534336079"&gt;(Regular Link&lt;/a&gt;) -- a little squarer than I'd like, but here's where the quality starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/mens-loafers/horsebit-loafers-brown-funchal-80746"&gt;Carmina Xim Last&lt;/a&gt; -- see, I told you. $330 for carminas is a great deal. I don't believe the Xim last is a true moccasin last, but it looks close enough to me. This would probably be my pick today.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gucci.com/us/en/pr/men/shoes-for-men/moccasins-and-loafers-for-men/1953-horsebit-leather-loafer-p-307929BLM001000?position=47&amp;amp;listName=ProductGrid&amp;amp;categoryPath=Men/Shoes-for-Men/Moccasins-and-Loafers-for-Men"&gt;Gucci 1953&lt;/a&gt; -- named for the year they invented the horsebit loafer, and in the original style (black calf, gold horsebit, moc toe). You're paying a little more here for the brand and for history, but they're still excellent shoes, and the price isn't &lt;em&gt;exorbitant&lt;/em&gt; -- this is a perfectly valid purchase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists</title><description>When is a coat like a blanket?

A belt or cinch allows you to play with a piece's silhouette, shaping a garment in fantastic ways.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/why-i-love-belted-coats-and-cinched-waists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5e10fee355327f1bff4c2430</guid><category>inspo</category><category>why I love</category><category>belted outerwear</category><category>cinched waist</category><category>corduroy</category><category>safari jackets</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>soft tailoring</category><category>casual</category><category>cardigans</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 16:42:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Stofa-Cinched-Waist-Safari-Jacket-1.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Stofa-Cinched-Waist-Safari-Jacket-1.jpg" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/G8Y8KHz"&gt;tl;dr: imgur album&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember when I first fell in love with belted coats, and I had to ask what they were called -- they're called &amp;quot;belted&amp;quot; coats. And belted cardigans. These items have a belt attached to the body, like a bath robe might, usually in the same material as the body material. This is not just an extra accessory; it allows you to play with the piece's silhouette, obtaining some benefits of both slim and full cuts. A cinched waist can do the same thing, shaping a garment in fantastic ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm going to explore why I love belted coats and cinched waists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an overview: a belt closure, unlike buttons and zippers, is inherently adjustable, giving you breathing room if you gain or lose weight, but also if you decide to wear a thick layer underneath, or just wear the coat over a tee shirt.It also makes it simple to close the coat, but &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; tightly, giving you one garment with multiple silhouette options. You can also, obviously, tie different knots, leave the coat open, with or without the belt, or in some cases, button the coat, making belted outerwear incredibly versatile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Belted-polo-coat--bespoke-from-Whitcomb---Shaftesbury---permanent-style-2.jpg" width="900" height="1350" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/raglan-sleeve-2.png" width="500" height="742" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/belted-overcoat-1.jpg" width="900" height="1350" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/document-robe-coat-2.jpg" width="900" height="1200" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Alexander-Burgh-going-back-to-bed-1.jpeg" width="900" height="1125" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Piti-Uomo-97-1.jpg" width="900" height="1125" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Overcoats, for the lazy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;How is an overcoat like a blanket?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Normally, an overcoat is a structured garment. There's a specific series of buttoning points, there's structure in the sholders, the lapels stay put, and you look like you're wearing a softer suit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A belt lets you mix things up. Instead of wearing the coat according to the rules, bury yourself in the coat like you would bury yourself in a blanket, and instead of fiddling with buttons, lazily tie it up into whatever seems like a knot to your hands at the time. Get a fabric that drapes in cool ways, and it'll flow around you in ways that simultaneously look and feel &lt;em&gt;super cozy&lt;/em&gt;. You want that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider a &lt;a href="https://dieworkwear.com/post/188593573349/the-other-kind-of-slip-on"&gt;raglan sleeve overcoat&lt;/a&gt; for even less of a structured look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/craftsman-clothing-open.jpg" width="1080" height="1349" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/acuratedman-Craftsman-Clothing.jpg" width="1080" height="1284" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Poszetka-Corduroy-Belted-Safari-Jacket-Arthur-II-1.jpg" width="533" height="800" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Poszetka-Green-Corduroy-Belted-Safari-Jacket-Arthur-II.jpg" width="366" height="550" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Belted-Safari-Jacket.jpg" width="675" height="1000" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Stofa-Cinched-Waist-Safari-Jacket.jpg" width="1080" height="1080" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mentioned safari jackets (and corduroy) in my previous post, but I've been dwelling on them since. Most are belted, but I really love the cinched waist on the Stoffa coat. As I mentioned before, they look great with a tie, but also dressed down, as they get a bit of the blanket vibe from the overcoat. They also look great in visibly soft materials like suede, corduroy, and linen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-gallery-card kg-width-wide kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-container"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-row"&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Umit-Benan-slippers.jpg" width="683" height="1025" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/Ethan-Wong-Noragi-2.jpg" width="427" height="640" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="kg-gallery-image"&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2020/01/hugh-heffner.jpg" width="942" height="1132" alt="Why I Love Belted Outerwear and Cinched Waists"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Throw these things on whenever you feel like you could use a little drip&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;A belt can also help a lighter garment echo loungewear. A &lt;a href="https://www.gentlemansgazette.com/dressing-gown/"&gt;dressing gown&lt;/a&gt; is not something you'd want to wear outside, but perhaps you want to replicate certain features to acheive &lt;a href="http://usuallywhatimdressed.in/inspiration/lazy-luxury/"&gt;lazy luxury&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A noragi approximates some of the same vibes while being a lot more acceptable to wear outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;p&gt;A belt or cinched waist can also help with parkas and leather jackets, as you will see in my full album below -- justifying a fuller cut that can fit over whatever you want to wear under it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, a belt or cinch allows you to play with one piece as though it was twelve, and have a lot of fun doing it. Consider one for your next piece of outerwear. Or cardigan. Or noragi. Or... Well, I won't begrudge you if you get them all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="a/G8Y8KHz"&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/G8Y8KHz"&gt;Why I Love -- Belted and Cinched&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Versatile, but not Minimal</title><description>As you move from a *basic* wardrobe to a more mature one, you will want some more unique pieces that stand out, or help you stand out. In this article, I intend to explore a few ways you might choose to build on your basic wardrobe while still keeping each piece versatile.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/versatile-but-not-minimal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5dfcd4f081ce9721bd3bf4a8</guid><category>guide</category><category>branching out</category><category>fun</category><category>bit loafers</category><category>safari jackets</category><category>loafers</category><category>casual</category><category>corduroy</category><category>chambray</category><category>variety</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 23:42:38 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/versatile.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/versatile.jpg" alt="Versatile, but not Minimal"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally, when you hear the word &amp;quot;versatile&amp;quot; in the world of menswear, you think of something very simple and minimal. Grey chinos. Dark wash jeans. White and light blue button ups. Minimal white sneakers, CP-style. Gray and navy overcoats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But is that what versatility is really about? For me, a key part of versatility is being able to wear something in casual, business casual, and somewhat more formal contexts. It also helps to have neutral colors and other details that pair well with a variety of options, but &lt;em&gt;minimalism&lt;/em&gt; isn't actually required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And versatility isn't just a nice idea. It allows you to invest more in a smaller number of higher-quality pieces, which is always a great thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As you move from a &lt;em&gt;basic&lt;/em&gt; wardrobe to a more mature one, you will want some more unique pieces that stand out, or help you stand out. In this article, I intend to explore a few ways you might choose to build on your basic wardrobe while still keeping each piece versatile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bvq-Jmfh4tq/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bvq-Jmfh4tq/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bvq-Jmfh4tq/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;Damn, I love these loafers. #bitloafers from @meerminmallorca  #socks from @anonymousism_japan  Worn with my @blacklapel #suit. Yes, you can wear moc-toe but loafers with a suit. #loafers #mensfashion #menswear #mensstyle #wiwt #ootd #shoes #classicmenswear #moccasins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/dresscodemenswear/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Daniel Hakimi&lt;/a&gt; (@dresscodemenswear) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-03-31T11:42:57+00:00"&gt;Mar 31, 2019 at 4:42am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="bitloafers"&gt;Bit Loafers&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1953, Aldo Gucci had a weird fucking idea. The history of menswear has always been linked to horseback riding, but he wanted to try something new. He took a metal horse bit—the thing they put into a horse's mouth to make sure it turns when you pull at the harness (yes, this is kind of horrible)—and he put it on a loafer. The original—a moccasin-style loafer in black calf with gold hardware—was an instant hit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mind you, a moccasin-style loafer is generally a very casual dress shoe. But the bit loafer was an expensive shoe in 1953, when the wealthy men were mostly white bankers and stuff like that—the types of men who wore suits. So that's how it was worn, and it's maintained a niche there as a different way to take any suit and make it a little bit flashier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But they still work great with shorts! See &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/DjxdOen"&gt;this pair&lt;/a&gt; in suede from &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Obcdmeme/"&gt;/u/Obcdmeme/&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/hLF7sHK"&gt;these Carminas&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/nipplemonger"&gt;/u/nipplemonger&lt;/a&gt;. The latter is an apron toe and a sleek last, but it still works!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I own the above Meermins in brown calf, and I love them. They're a statement piece, but one I'm never afraid to wear to work, to parties, on the weekend... I can wholeheartedly recommend bit loafers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bf8DmaZAqlM/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bf8DmaZAqlM/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/Bf8DmaZAqlM/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;Which autumnal hue strikes a cord with you? 🍁🍂🎸 #Corduroys#FallFashion #BrooksBrothers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/brooksbrothers.australia/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Brooks Brothers Australia&lt;/a&gt; (@brooksbrothers.australia) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2018-03-05T10:35:21+00:00"&gt;Mar 5, 2018 at 2:35am PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="corduroys"&gt;Corduroys&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playing with texture is fun. Corduroy is chino's softer, tufted cousin, with a striped wale texture. It's velvet, except much more wearable and easier to maintain. And although denim, chino, and wool are treated as the most basic and common trouser materials, there's nothing Corduroy can't do. I'm generally recommending &amp;quot;corduroys&amp;quot;—that is to say, corduroy trousers—but of course, these are just ideas, and a corduroy jacket or shirt might take you far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dress it up with soft tailoring, or down with knitwear or a flannel. Pair it with suede. Seek inspiration from &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/thisishirokisamerica"&gt;/u/thisishirokisamerica&lt;/a&gt;, who made two inspo albums on the material—&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/0rEcDeR"&gt;CorduRoy G. Biv&lt;/a&gt;, organized by color, and &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/Cu4hN7r"&gt;Corduroy Boy But Make It Spring/Summer&lt;/a&gt;. It's no wonder reddit has fallen in love with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just choose your pair carefully. Color is the obvious factor: corduroy takes on color well, enabling things like a bright orange, but an orange pair might be less versatile than a navy blue. But also consider pocket layout. Slant pockets are probably more versatile, whereas the five-pocket layout forces a casual appearance. It might also be worth considering wale width. Trousers generally use a wider wale, and jackets and shirts a narrower wale, but again, this is up to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With that warning, I arm you with knowledge: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/ay06yb/your_favorite_for_corduroy_pants/"&gt;use these brand recommendations wisely&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/BsOcwQShWU4/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/BsOcwQShWU4/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/BsOcwQShWU4/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;The 003 Field Jacket in a rich burgundy suede.  #LaStoffa //&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/stoffa/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; stòffa&lt;/a&gt; (@stoffa) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-01-04T20:18:13+00:00"&gt;Jan 4, 2019 at 12:18pm PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="safarijackets"&gt;Safari Jackets&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A safari jacket can, likewise, be dressed up or down. You can't really wear it over a suit or blazer, but it can look great with a tie, an open collar, a turtleneck, or a &lt;a href="https://streetxsprezza.wordpress.com/2019/04/07/the-jaunty-scarf/"&gt;jaunty scarf&lt;/a&gt;. Fashionbeans called it &lt;a href="https://www.fashionbeans.com/article/safari-jacket-men/"&gt;2018’s Most Stylish And Practical Menswear Item&lt;/a&gt;... although the article currently says 2019, and I assume it will say 2020 soon enough, because they think they'll sell you more if they lie and pretend they just wrote the article five minutes ago... But still, Safari Jackets are interesting and cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The above &amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://stoffa.co/products/outerwear-003-field-jacket"&gt;field jacket&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; from Stoffa features a beautiful cinched waist. A safari jacket generally also has four pockets, and might also have lapels with large notches, or a few other features—the definition is certainly a little ambiguous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6SBpu_pLQZ/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="12" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6SBpu_pLQZ/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"/&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt; View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p style=" margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B6SBpu_pLQZ/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;" target="_blank"&gt;I&amp;#39;m having a texture party! You are cord-ially invited. Got a favorite winter texture? #nosilkallowed Tie bar: @tusk_bar (link in bio) Shirt: @ratioclothing  Lapel pin (&amp;#34;the&amp;#34;): @thehill_side  Lapel pin (🔵): @thetiebar Corduroy jacket: @officinegenerale  Tie: @weekendcasual  #dressedchest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;A post shared by &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thedressedchest/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px;" target="_blank"&gt; Rainier Jonn&lt;/a&gt; (@thedressedchest) on &lt;time style=" font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;" datetime="2019-12-20T04:57:52+00:00"&gt;Dec 19, 2019 at 8:57pm PST&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src="//www.instagram.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="chambrayshirts"&gt;Chambray Shirts&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chambray—denim's softer cousin—is one of the menswear crowd's favorite magic tricks. It echoes workwear, making for a shirt that looks perfectly good untucked in the summer, but just watch &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/thedressedchest/"&gt;@thedressedchest&lt;/a&gt; wear it with a tie under corduroy above. Or check &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/B3OmUdFD-TD/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to see it under a denim blazer. Crazy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chambray is one of those textures that can provide complexity without taking up too much attention. See &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/CPGfNmV"&gt;this take&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/DebonaireGamer/"&gt;/u/debonairegamer&lt;/a&gt;. Pay attention not only to shade and drape but collar style, pocket layout, plackets, stitching, wrinkling, and body length.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a reason Put This On called chambray a &amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://putthison.com/chambray-a-workhorse-casual-shirt/"&gt;workhorse&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; And Ethan Wong got &lt;a href="https://streetxsprezza.wordpress.com/2018/07/01/an-ode-to-denim-and-chambray-shirts/"&gt;a little obsessed&lt;/a&gt;. Maybe you can be too. &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/8zvxdh/your_favorite_for_chambray_shirts/"&gt;Here are some recommendations&lt;/a&gt;. Be careful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="havefunexploring"&gt;Have Fun Exploring!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, I can't tell you how to branch out. I don't expect you to buy all of the above—I don't have everything I listed above myself. These were just ideas to help get your creative juices flowing. If you're branching out past your basic wardrobe, it's important for you to branch out and make your own choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So hopefully, I've gotten you thinking less about the exact styles above, and more about interesting textures, metal hardware, a cinched waist, and wearing things you haven't worn before. Good luck, and have fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>A Visit to Leffot in New York City</title><description>Leffot was just across the street, and yesterday was a beautiful day, so I popped right over for a quick look at their selection.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/a-visit-to-leffot-in-new-york-city/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5df94f8d82f26b3e77b0c3dd</guid><category>store visit</category><category>shoes</category><category>nyc</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>dress shoes</category><category>menswear</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/leffot.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="a/GDWzY5g"&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/GDWzY5g"&gt;Leffot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/leffot.jpg" alt="A Visit to Leffot in New York City"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went to J. Fitzpatrick's sample sale yesterday -- Justin is a cool dude, btw. I had some old photos of his store on my old phone, but that thing is dead now, so you don't get to see photos. Suffice it to say, you want some J. Fitzpatricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leffot is just across the street, and yesterday was a beautiful day, so I popped right over for a quick look at their selection. There were some nice Aldens and &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/GDWzY5g"&gt;Corthays&lt;/a&gt;, some &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/AAWcd9H"&gt;scarves from Drake's&lt;/a&gt;, and a &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/SvHV6Yc"&gt;very large wheel of Pantherella socks&lt;/a&gt;. They had &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/pev0pcb"&gt;horns made of horn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/dg9sMJV"&gt;house slippers from Hiro Yanagimachi&lt;/a&gt;, creams, nice photos... It was all very nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Corthay -- today (Thursday) and tomorrow, Leffot his hosting a Corthay trunk show, so if you have money to blow, go get some dope, unique shoes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also -- &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/0cy7BmI"&gt;I bought something!&lt;/a&gt; Take your guesses as to what's in that bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>A Glossary of Dress Shoe Styles -- Names, Photos, and Descriptions</title><description>I started writing this guide in an attempt to catch everything worth catching. I ended up running into more styles than I could really hope to capture... But hopefully, this is good enough.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/a-glossary-of-dress-shoe-styles-names-photos-and-descriptions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5df94f8d82f26b3e77b0c3de</guid><category>dress shoes</category><category>shoes</category><category>boots</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>definitions</category><category>guide</category><category>loafers</category><category>menswear</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/parkave.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;h1 id="toeshapestyles"&gt;Toe Shape Styles&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/parkave.jpg" alt="A Glossary of Dress Shoe Styles -- Names, Photos, and Descriptions"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although I'm listing these as distinct styles, it's better to not categorize these, but think of them as a spectrum. As you grow to appreciate footwear, you'll start paying more attention to specific &amp;quot;lasts,&amp;quot; IE shoe molds, and take note of how round or elongated each one is. But for the sake of the glossary:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.gethypervisual.com/images/shopify/5f5237d1-30a7-498b-9d23-e0053fcfbe09/w1200_89f9_j-fitzpatrick-footwear-march-2016-ss-16-magnolia-dark-brown-museum-calf-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Classic Round&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Standard, dressy, classic, never wrong.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://smhttp-ssl-39255.nexcesscdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Round-toe_shoes.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Truly Round&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  The classic &amp;quot;round&amp;quot; shoe last has some shape to it; this extreme is just a smooth oval. More casual-- you'll see this more on moc-toe loafers than anywhere -- but still fairly versatile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.trickers.com/pub/media/catalog/product/cache/e4d64343b1bc593f1c5348fe05efa4a6/w/o/woodstock_5636_antique_qtr.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bulbous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Casual.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.gethypervisual.com/images/shopify/5f5237d1-30a7-498b-9d23-e0053fcfbe09/w1200_86a9_j-fitzpatrick-footwear-collection-7-june-2017-hero-0507.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Slight Point / Elongated Round&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Sleeker and more elegant than classic round. Less versatile, sometimes harder to pull off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61owbNB03aL._UX575_.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ugly shoes and wizard boots; avoid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://vass-shoes.com/sites/default/files/styles/shoes_front_page_collection/public/shoes/5069-s-museum_plum-single_sole.jpg?itok=Kbp0aZoJ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chisel Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Comes close to a point, but squares off near the end. Weirdly a lot better than point or square. Dressy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stacyadams.com/shop/images/21187-221.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Square&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ugly. Used by cheap shoes. Ferragamo is famous for making these look not that bad, and distinctive... But still not good.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="lacedshoestyles"&gt;Laced Shoe Styles&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started writing this guide in an attempt to catch everything worth catching. I ended up running into more styles than I could really hope to capture... But hopefully, this is good enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/captoe_oxfords_burgundy_boxcalf_594_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oxfords&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (See also &lt;a href="https://www.gentlemansgazette.com/balmoral-boots/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Balmoral Boots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). Oxfords are shoes with closed lacing. &amp;quot;Balmoral&amp;quot; actually means there is a horizontal line around the shoe or boot.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/media/catalog/product/cache/2/image/924x805/17f82f742ffe127f42dca9de82fb58b1/N/e/Newbury_915_NIGCALF_main.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wholecut&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A beautiful style that puts the quality of the leather on display. People disagree about how formal these are; some argue they're more formal than cap toe oxfords, since they're simpler, and others argue that they're more casual, because they show wear more. Note that, in black patent leather, these are one of three valid options for black tie appropriate footwear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.allenedmonds.com/dw/image/v2/AAXI_PRD/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-allenedmonds-catalog/default/dwe37b2ea5/images/2.1/mens-shoes/mackenzie-3446-walnut-pair-web.jpg?sw=736&amp;amp;sh=736&amp;amp;sm=fit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medallion Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Can come with a number of features, but here is the pure, almost wholecut, medallion toe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://www.allenedmonds.com/dw/image/v2/AAXI_PRD/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-allenedmonds-catalog/default/dwc9a0b056/images/2.1/mens-shoes/carlyle-8833-darkchili-angle-web.jpg?sw=736&amp;amp;sh=736&amp;amp;sm=fit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plain Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; The plain toe oxford is kinda dumb. It's not as classic as the cap toe, but it's also missing the sleekness of the wholecut. It's not bad, it's just not really the best of anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.allenedmonds.com/dw/image/v2/AAXI_PRD/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-allenedmonds-catalog/default/dw019394d1/images/2.1/mens-shoes/parkave-5615-black-pair-web.jpg?sw=2000&amp;amp;sh=2000&amp;amp;sm=fit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cap Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Absolute staple in black. The quintessential boring business shoe and suit complement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/captoe-oxfords_brown_80201_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perforated Cap Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Note that it's somewhat hard to draw the lines between a PCT, quarter brogue, and semi brogue, but generally, I would say that the PCT is just a cap toe with perforations, a quarter brogue adds perforations around the quarters of the shoe, and a semi brogue adds a medallion. A wingtip swaps out the cap toe for a particular pattern, which you'll see.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/adelaide_oxfords_shoes_burgundy_museum_80512_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quarter Brogue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/mens-oxford-shoes/lace-up-semi-brogue-brown-10051"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semi Brogue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Brogue&lt;/strong&gt; / &lt;strong&gt;Wingtip&lt;/strong&gt; -- replace the cap toe with a curvy &amp;quot;wing&amp;quot; pattern.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/oxford_shoes_tan_922_carmina_l-7.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shortwing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Notice how the wings curve down at the middle of the shoe?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Longwing&lt;/strong&gt; / &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Gunboat&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot; (I couldn't find a photo of longwing oxfords, please share one if you have one. Here, the lines extend from the wings, horizontally, all the way to the back. This also makes them &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;balmorals&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot; People tend to call all oxfords balmorals, but balmoral refers specifically to the existence of a horizontal line like on a longwing oxford.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/austerity_brogue_brown_80270_l-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Austerity&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Brogue&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; Wingtips &lt;em&gt;without&lt;/em&gt; brouging, and without the medallion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluchers&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Derbies&lt;/strong&gt; (See also derby/blucher boots, including &lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/shoes/banbury-dark-oak-antique-calf-202-last.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;chukka boots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). Technically different, bluchers and derbies both have open lacing and tend to be lumped together. Bluchers and Derbies are noticeably more casual than oxfords.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.styleforum.net/data/attachments/759/759578-b9916dc7ba7c9368e4451214a1af4b15.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plain Toe&lt;/strong&gt; / &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;PTBs&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; Plain Toe Bluchers -- particularly in a dark color with a contrasting welt as shown here, and with a round or bulbous toe -- are reddit standards. See Tricker's Robert (shown here in black shell) and &lt;a href="https://i.ebayimg.com/images/g/WbEAAOSwceVdO0vW/s-l1600.jpg"&gt;Alden's Color 8 Shell PTBs&lt;/a&gt;. Note that &lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/derby_shoes_black_carmina_80449_l.jpg"&gt;plain toe derbies&lt;/a&gt; also exist, but I'd prefer a blucher.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://aldenmadison.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/2160.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cap Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Kinda silly; meant for oxfords. Not wrong or bad, just not the best in its class.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/mens-derby-shoes/captoe-derby-brown-soft-grain-748"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perforated Cap Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Derbies here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://vass-shoes.com/sites/default/files/styles/shoes_front_page_collection/public/shoes/5100-f-museum_brown-single_sole.jpg?itok=fP1OdbO-"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quarter Brouge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/shoes/cardiff-horween-cordovan-black-202-last.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semi Brogue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Brogue&lt;/strong&gt; / &lt;strong&gt;Wingtip&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.trickers.com/pub/media/catalog/product/cache/ecd051e9670bd57df35c8f0b122d8aea/7/2/7292_1_keswick_top_original_65796_1.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shortwing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Much more common. ]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i1.wp.com/fromsqualortoballer.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/DSCF3898.jpg?w=1995&amp;amp;ssl=1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Longwing&lt;/strong&gt; / &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Gunboat&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; Longwing bluchers are a Reddit favorite, particularly vintage Florsheim Imperials. Note that there's technically no such thing as a longwing derby.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.imgur.com/86CHa5a.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Austerity&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Brogue&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; -- Boots, because this was the only good photo I could find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.nordstrommedia.com/ImageGallery/store/product/Zoom/3/_103847743.jpg?h=365&amp;amp;w=240&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;quality=45&amp;amp;fit=fill&amp;amp;fm=jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apron Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0277/2511/products/Lof-_-Tung-Grant-16124-Dark-brown-utah-Calf-T-Last_1.jpg?v=1558105933"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moc Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/nowegian_shoes_brown_757_EEE_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norweigan Split-Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A more casual style than many realize; deceptively tricky to wear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.nordstrommedia.com/ImageGallery/store/product/Zoom/7/_102290987.jpg?h=365&amp;amp;w=240&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;quality=45&amp;amp;fit=fill&amp;amp;fm=jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bicycle Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Dumb-looking, associated with cheap shoes. Avoid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="sliponshoes"&gt;Slip-on shoes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://wildsmith.com/img/main_shoe_images/windsor-mocha.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loafers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A loafer is a slip-on dress shoe with a rigid sole, heel, and seam around the front.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Construction Style&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://wildsmith.com/img/main_shoe_images/windsor-mocha.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Lasted from the top down, like traditional laced dress shoes. Generally dressy. Invented by Wildsmith Shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.imgur.com/zNsleCi.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moccasin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Lasted from the bottom up, like actual moccasins. Generally casual. Invented by Aurland Shoes. Yes, this photograph is of my feet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://belgianshoes.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/10/mr_casual_suede_7.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Belgian&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Derived from velvet dress slippers. Invented by Belgian Shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toe Styles&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://wildsmith.com/img/main_shoe_images/windsor-mocha.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apron Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Thin seam, top-down construction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.imgur.com/zNsleCi.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moc Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A thicker seam, associated with moccasin construction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/black_penny_loafers_80190_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Split Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; That seam down the front.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stacyadams.com/shop/images/21187-221.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bicycle Toe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ugly, associated with cheap shoes as discussed above. Avoid. Not really even loafers, by my definition, since the seam doesn't go around all the way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vamp Styles&lt;/strong&gt;. Most loafers are named by the vamp style.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://224220-www.web.tornado-node.net/assets/uploads/2019/03/aurlands18022-2560x1440.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Penny Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Classic ivy style. Invented by &lt;a href="https://wildsmith.com/img/main_shoe_images/windsor-mocha.jpg"&gt;Wildsmith&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://224220-www.web.tornado-node.net/assets/uploads/2019/03/aurlands18022-2560x1440.jpg"&gt;Aurland&lt;/a&gt; shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://brooksbrothers.scene7.com/is/image/BrooksBrothers/033H_BURGUNDY?$bbenlarged$"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tassel Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Invented by Alden + Brooks Brothers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.pinimg.com/736x/39/0a/07/390a0701bbcd6b3d830dd10756e1f1f1--loafers.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kilted Tassel Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. God, these look dumb. I spent longer than I expected looking for one that didn't look &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; dumb, but they all look dumb.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://brooksbrothers.scene7.com/is/image/BrooksBrothers/MH00153_TAN_3?$bbenlarged$"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Venetian Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (plain). Almost always moc toe. Generally a cheap style, although not as bad as bicycle toe. Note that plain-vamp Belgian loafers are not called &amp;quot;Venetian&amp;quot; loafers, because that would be weird. Also, for some reason, Brooks Brothers calls these &amp;quot;American Loafers,&amp;quot; maybe because the moccasin style is American... But that's all quite confusing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://media.gucci.com/style/DarkGray_Center_0_0_2400x2400/1439376067/307929_BLM00_1000_003_100_0000_Light-1953-Horsebit-leather-loafer.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Horsebit / Bit / Gucci Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Invented by Aldo Gucci. Modern bit loafers are more common in an &lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/mens-loafers/horsebit-loafers-black-80643"&gt;apron toe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://belgianshoes.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/10/mr_casual_allcalf_5.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Exclusively for Belgian loafers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/string_suede_loafer_carmina_80228_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;String Loafer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Carmina in Snuff Suede is the classic. Casual style.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i1.adis.ws/i/tom_ford/J1060T-VSP_NER_OS_C?$large$&amp;amp;bg=rgb(255,255,255)"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A few high-fashion designers like Tom Ford are trying to make this a thing now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Slippers&lt;/strong&gt; / &amp;quot;&lt;strong&gt;Wholecut Loafers&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;quot; Not what most people call &amp;quot;slippers.&amp;quot;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/slippers_black_pantent_80445_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Black patent leather opera pumps with a grosgrain or satin bow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Yes, all of those elements are important -- do you want your shoe to be a. black tie appropriate or b. ugly?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/media/catalog/product/cache/1/image/924x805/17f82f742ffe127f42dca9de82fb58b1/R/o/Royal_Albert_389_BURVEL_main.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Velvet / Prince Albert / Smoking Slippers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In plain black, these are black tie appropriate. In any other color or with any crest/medallion/piping/embroidering, they are not -- they're just flashy as hell. Maybe good for creative black tie, for your fancy dinner party, or for your weird fashionny look.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.edwardgreen.com/shop/media/catalog/product/cache/1/image/924x805/17f82f742ffe127f42dca9de82fb58b1/A/l/Albert_389_NAVSKID_main.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suede Slippers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Cool stuff. Some argue that black suede is a good substitute for black velvet in black tie. Not traditional, but you'll pass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0211/7310/products/AAD3m4ps2w8aOqdL5eukLA6eNJNFzeE9NvH6ZMg5lynxGwcdjyzffNKo7pv6Okng99f2CXLgA6-xUzx2ifbkUEKie8OKToPUteTAiV4JDNefVfEXJ31YfExxFdOzkmsGUCOhEpYAmpkahlbkTmjY1y6rDA8Dj5Hy4L_A7JuJTz4zbxTSdHvRZlRSxnjrj_pCBPsvVI7t_2048x1400.jpg?v=1540482231"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smooth Leather Slippers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Unusual. See Viberg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0019/6539/1983/products/mens-kilim-loafers-MKLF41-0064_1024x1024@2x.jpg?v=1551203053"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kilim Slippers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Okay, I guess you can't call these dress shoes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="elasticclosure"&gt;Elastic Closure&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These shoes are arguably still slip-ons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://dhb3yazwboecu.cloudfront.net/909/chelsea_boots_black_box_calf_80186_l.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chelsea boots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ideally wholecut, or near wholecut, with a seam at the bottom of the elastic. Versatile, to the point where the same pair can potentially be worn with jeans or a suit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href="https://www-saintcrispins-com.exactdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/21955_1.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;lossy=1&amp;amp;fit=2500%2C2500&amp;amp;ssl=1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lazyman Oxfords&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; A lot of very high-end shoemakers (Saint Crispin's, in this case) have been making oxford-lookalike shoes with elastic closures and faux lacing. They're an interesting oddity here; you might expect these to carry the same connotation as a pre-tied bow tie, but... They're one of those things that's acceptable only because the brands doing it are highly respected British brands, and because they are, they're practically conservative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="buckleclosure"&gt;Buckle Closure&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the below shoes look best with a plain toe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://meermin.com/media/catalog/product/cache/image/e9c3970ab036de70892d86c6d221abfe/1/0/10157420140000SE-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Single Monkstrap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Shown here with a medallion toe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.carminashoemaker.us/monk-strap-shoes/double-monk-strap-burgundy-80544"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double Monkstrap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Shown here with a cap toe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://meermin.com/media/catalog/product/cache/image/e9c3970ab036de70892d86c6d221abfe/1/0/10157420140000SE-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double Monk Boot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ankle boots.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://meermin.com/media/catalog/product/cache/image/600x800/e9c3970ab036de70892d86c6d221abfe/1/0/10149911130000HE-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jodhpur Boot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. On paper, less dressy than Chelsea boots. In practice, nobody will know the difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="buttonclosure"&gt;Button Closure&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0076/3674/6355/products/j-fitzpatrick-footwear-collection-15-november-2017-01_1024x1024_34c99d20-fffb-4832-ae2e-662c4aebe57c_1024x1024@2x.jpg?v=1542626760"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Button Boots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="zipper"&gt;Zipper&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://i.imgur.com/nbyJdzt.jpg"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side-zip Boots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In the same class as Chelseas and Jodhpurs, a sleek boot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dual-closure Boots&lt;/strong&gt;. That is to say, any boot with a zipper and also some other closure. Like a chelsea with a zipper on one side, or something like that. Silly; avoid.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>A Visit to Supply &amp; Advise in Miami</title><description>Upscale menswear shop that has a dual personality. On the first floor you'll find Americana and military-inspired collections. On the second floor, you'll be wooed by their top notch suiting collection featuring brands like Ring Jacket, Hamilton, Drake's, etc.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/a-visit-to-supply/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5df94f8d82f26b3e77b0c3d9</guid><category>store visit</category><category>classic menswear</category><category>menswear</category><category>miami</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/supply.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="a/voNJ2ZA"&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/voNJ2ZA"&gt;Supply &amp; Advise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/supply.jpg" alt="A Visit to Supply &amp; Advise in Miami"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I took a trip to Miami. It wasn't a vacation... It was a family emergency, but it was a month-long emergency, so I found myself needing a break. I was fortunate enough to be in an apartment just blocks away from Supply and Advise, so I went over there a couple of times and took photos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As /u/mcadamsandwich described it in the local shopping megathread:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.supplyandadvise.com/"&gt;Supply &amp;amp; Advise&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upscale menswear shop that has a dual personality (like most of us) - on the first floor you'll find Americana and military-inspired collections featuring brands like Alden, RRL, orSlow, The Real McCoys, Filson, etc. Take the elevator to the second floor to be wooed by their top notch suiting collection featuring brands like Ring Jacket, Hamilton, Drake's, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jonathan and Kevin are super friendly and helpful. Highly recommended!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favorite pieces were Drake's grenadines and ancient madders... And also a GBV camp collar shirt that fit me shockingly well -- a little long in the body but otherwise beautifully. But none of that was on sale... And I can't really afford their regular prices. Still, they were nice to me and poured me some of that Hibiki 12 year, so I'm going to do the least I can do and post about it here. And tell you to visit, or to buy something from their website -- you'll be glad you did. (Especially if you catch a good sale).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was a little more focused on the second floor. The first floor had plenty of goodies from EG, Unis (low stock right now, but more coming), 8.15, Beams+, GBV, and everything /u/mcadamsandwich mentioned. They also mentioned to me that they're bringing in some 100 Hands shirting pretty soon -- they make great fucking shirts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other pieces of note not featured in my album included bombers and shirting from Beams+, seersucker from GBV, Velva Sheen tees and a sweatshirt, and cotton piqué / marcella shirting from Ring Jacket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Off Kilter: An Asymmetry Inspiration Album</title><description>Asymmetry is largely about weirdness, to me. It's about going off-balance on purpose, on throwing away classic silhouettes and predictable patterns for something that clashes with itself, and demands a new perspective. You're going to see a lot of weird shit in this album. Enjoy.  </description><link>http://localhost:2368/off-kilter-an-asymmetry-inspiration-album/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5df94f8d82f26b3e77b0c3d6</guid><category>asymmetry</category><category>inspo</category><dc:creator>Daniel Hakimi</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 01:17:00 GMT</pubDate><media:content url="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/asymmetry.jpg" medium="image"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-embed-card"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="imgur-embed-pub" lang="en" data-id="a/91JP6w7"&gt;&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/a/91JP6w7"&gt;Off Kilter: An Asymmetry Inspiration Album&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;script async src="//s.imgur.com/min/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;!--kg-card-begin: markdown--&gt;&lt;img src="http://localhost:2368/content/images/2019/12/asymmetry.jpg" alt="Off Kilter: An Asymmetry Inspiration Album"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a bit of a personal story. I initially told the story through the inspiration album, but I reproduced it here in plain text as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symmetry has always been something people appreciate, whether consciously or not. This is true not only in clothing, but everything, from nature, to fine art, to facial expressions. A lot of studies show that facial symmetry is a huge factor in attractiveness, and that people treat attractive people better everywhere, not just in romance, so... It seems like it might be important.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If symmetry is so important, I want to talk about the reasons a fashion designer might avoid it, and what we can get out of that. I hope it's as interesting to all of you as it is to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Asymmetry is largely about weirdness, to me. It's about going off-balance on purpose, on throwing away classic silhouettes and predictable patterns for something that clashes with itself, and demands a new perspective. You're going to see a lot more weird shit in this album. Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facial symmetry is supposed to be important... but no face is 100% symmetrical. There's always some imperfection, some... wabi-sabi to a person's face. Cindy Crawford is famous for the mole that got her teased as a kid. How much imperfection is the right amount? How much is too much?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mentioned the importance of facial symmetry for a reason. Back in 2012, I came down with a case of Bell's Palsy. Bell's Palsy is a weird little disease; basically, one nerve in your face gets paralyzed, and half of your face stops working right. It usually occurs once, at random, and usually only lasts a couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bell's Palsy fucks with both your conscious and subconscious control of your face. It fucks with your smile. You know, worse things have happened -- it's not going to kill me, it's not going to stop me from doing much, so I have to count my blessings... But not being able to smile properly, it has all sorts of weird psychological effects They say smiling actually makes you happier -- well, when you get self-conscious about your smile, you smile less. And if you know facial symmetry is important to how you're perceived... Friends will say they don't notice, but others will say that they love your smirk. Strangers on the internet will say they hate your smirk, and they'd prefer if you just smiled. So yeah, people notice, they just don't understand what it is they're looking at. You don't necessarily understand, yourself, when you look in the mirror. Not being able to smile, man... It fucks with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My case of Bell's Palsy was not so simple as others. I had it briefly a couple of times when I was a kid, but it came and went. It happened again in 2012. My neurologist told me not to worry, until a short while later, when we realized it was permanent. She said the closest thing we had to a solution was a nerve graft, and... I don't know if you've heard the words &amp;quot;nerve graft&amp;quot; before, but they're two scary fucking words.  At this point, even if my seventh facial nerve started working again, the muscles it controls probably couldn't do what I'd need them to do. It's a part of me now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;----&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, we can fight the wabi-sabi, ignore it, or embrace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For further reading, I'd recommend &lt;a href="https://ssense.com/en-us/editorial/fashion/off-balance-on-purpose-fashions-sacred-geometry"&gt;Erika Houle's piece at ssense&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--kg-card-end: markdown--&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>